[
  {
    "id": 501,
    "question": "pena",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Qué pena que no tuvieran este vestido en mi talla!.",
    "answer": "shame, sentence, pity",
    "answerDetails": "It’s a shame that they didn’t have this dress in my size."
  },
  {
    "id": 502,
    "question": "pueda",
    "questionDetails": "Lo más que pueda.",
    "answer": "can",
    "answerDetails": "As much as you can."
  },
  {
    "id": 503,
    "question": "única",
    "questionDetails": "He buscado la camiseta blanca perfecta por una eternidad, y ésta es la única.",
    "answer": "only one",
    "answerDetails": "I’ve searched forever for the perfect white T-shirt, and this is the only one."
  },
  {
    "id": 504,
    "question": "gustaría",
    "questionDetails": "Me gustaría que tuvieras compañía.",
    "answer": "wish, ‘d, would",
    "answerDetails": "I wish you had company."
  },
  {
    "id": 505,
    "question": "puta",
    "questionDetails": "Es puta por naturaleza.",
    "answer": "whore, bitch, fucking",
    "answerDetails": "She is whore by nature."
  },
  {
    "id": 506,
    "question": "pienso",
    "questionDetails": "Les damos a nuestros pollos solamente pienso orgánico.",
    "answer": "feed, fodder, dry dog food",
    "answerDetails": "We give our chickens only organic feed."
  },
  {
    "id": 507,
    "question": "acaba",
    "questionDetails": "Me lo acaba de decir.",
    "answer": "just, ends, finish",
    "answerDetails": "It just told me."
  },
  {
    "id": 508,
    "question": "queremos",
    "answer": "Want"
  },
  {
    "id": 509,
    "question": "estaban",
    "answer": "they were"
  },
  {
    "id": 510,
    "question": "lejos",
    "questionDetails": "Pero ya estabas lejos.",
    "answer": "far",
    "answerDetails": "But you were already far."
  },
  {
    "id": 511,
    "question": "palabra",
    "questionDetails": "Lo dijiste palabra por palabra.",
    "answer": "word",
    "answerDetails": "It was quoted word by word."
  },
  {
    "id": 512,
    "question": "puesto",
    "questionDetails": "Deberías solicitar ese puesto.",
    "answer": "post, position",
    "answerDetails": "You should apply for that post."
  },
  {
    "id": 513,
    "question": "luz",
    "questionDetails": "Bailamos a la luz de la luna.",
    "answer": "light, power",
    "answerDetails": "We danced by the light of the moon."
  },
  {
    "id": 514,
    "question": "viste",
    "questionDetails": "¿Pepe tiene novia nueva?-¡ No sé! ¿Con quién estaba cuando lo viste?",
    "answer": "you saw him, did you see, you watched",
    "answerDetails": "Does Pepe have a new girlfriend?-I don’t know! Who was he with when you saw him?"
  },
  {
    "id": 515,
    "question": "adónde",
    "questionDetails": "¿Adónde va este tren?",
    "answer": "where",
    "answerDetails": "Where is this train headed?"
  },
  {
    "id": 516,
    "question": "vivo",
    "questionDetails": "El color rojo vivo de su logo atrae la atención.",
    "answer": "vivid",
    "answerDetails": "The vivid red color of your logo catches the eye."
  },
  {
    "id": 517,
    "question": "normal",
    "questionDetails": "Él es un tipo normal, no un gatito glamour.",
    "answer": "regular",
    "answerDetails": "He’s a regular guy, not a glamour puss."
  },
  {
    "id": 518,
    "question": "vienen",
    "questionDetails": "¿Has hablado con los Robinson?-Sí, vienen esta noche.",
    "answer": "they are coming",
    "answerDetails": "Have you heard from the Robinsons?-Yes, they are coming tonight."
  },
  {
    "id": 519,
    "question": "raro",
    "questionDetails": "Es raro que 1 niño de su edad tenga tanta habilidad natural para tocar jazz.",
    "answer": "uncommon",
    "answerDetails": "It’s uncommon for a child of his age to have so much natural ability to play jazz."
  },
  {
    "id": 520,
    "question": "ido",
    "questionDetails": "Es como si no estuvieras aquí. Pareces estar ido.",
    "answer": "miles away",
    "answerDetails": "It’s as if you weren’t here. You seem to be miles away."
  },
  {
    "id": 521,
    "question": "tuyo",
    "questionDetails": "Sabes, la gente está diciendo que es tuyo.",
    "answer": "yours",
    "answerDetails": "You know, folks are saying he’s yours."
  },
  {
    "id": 522,
    "question": "dime",
    "questionDetails": "Dime lo que quieres hacer.",
    "answer": "tell me",
    "answerDetails": "Tell me what you want to do."
  },
  {
    "id": 523,
    "question": "quieras",
    "questionDetails": "Podemos comprar lo que quieras.",
    "answer": "want",
    "answerDetails": "We can get whatever you want, you know?"
  },
  {
    "id": 524,
    "question": "seas",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero que no seas infeliz.",
    "answer": "be",
    "answerDetails": "I want you not to be unhappy."
  },
  {
    "id": 525,
    "question": "hablamos",
    "questionDetails": "Hablamos acerca de Antonio, y nos damos cuenta que nosotros 2 habíamos salido con él.",
    "answer": "we talked",
    "answerDetails": "We talked about Antonio, and we realized we had both dated him."
  },
  {
    "id": 526,
    "question": "meter",
    "questionDetails": "Los empleados pueden meter un porcentaje de su salario previo a impuestos.",
    "answer": "tuck, cram, squeeze",
    "answerDetails": "Employees can tuck away a percentage of their pretax salary."
  },
  {
    "id": 527,
    "question": "niños",
    "questionDetails": "Unos Niños aprenden más rápido que otros.",
    "answer": "some kids",
    "answerDetails": "Some kids learn faster than others."
  },
  {
    "id": 528,
    "question": "allí",
    "questionDetails": "Estaré allí en como una hora. ¿Traigo algo?",
    "answer": "over",
    "answerDetails": "I’ll be over in about an hour. Should I bring anything?"
  },
  {
    "id": 529,
    "question": "mayor",
    "questionDetails": "El mayor océano del mundo es el Pacífico.",
    "answer": "largest, major, biggest",
    "answerDetails": "The world’s largest ocean is the Pacific Ocean."
  },
  {
    "id": 530,
    "question": "oportunidad",
    "questionDetails": "Aprovecha la oportunidad de estudiar en el extranjero.",
    "answer": "opportunity",
    "answerDetails": "Take the opportunity to study abroad."
  },
  {
    "id": 531,
    "question": "trabajando",
    "questionDetails": "Es un sistema unificado trabajando unido.",
    "answer": "working, workin’, laboring",
    "answerDetails": "It is a unified system working together."
  },
  {
    "id": 532,
    "question": "calle",
    "questionDetails": "Plano de calles.",
    "answer": "street",
    "answerDetails": "Street map."
  },
  {
    "id": 533,
    "question": "baño",
    "questionDetails": "Se dieron un baño en Ik Kil, un cenote en la Riviera Maya.",
    "answer": "swim, water closet",
    "answerDetails": "They went for a swim in Ik Kil, a natural sinkhole in the Mayan Riviera."
  },
  {
    "id": 534,
    "question": "tema",
    "questionDetails": "¿Podemos cambiar el tema? No quiero hablar más de eso.",
    "answer": "topic, subject, issue",
    "answerDetails": "Can we change the topic? I don’t want to talk about that anymore."
  },
  {
    "id": 535,
    "question": "sino",
    "questionDetails": "No una vez sino 2.",
    "answer": "but, fate",
    "answerDetails": "Not once but twice."
  },
  {
    "id": 536,
    "question": "darle",
    "questionDetails": "Es la primera vez que Charlie hace este trabajo. Tenemos que darle tiempo para adaptarse.",
    "answer": "give him",
    "answerDetails": "Charlie is new to the job. We need to give him time to adjust."
  },
  {
    "id": 537,
    "question": "demasiado",
    "questionDetails": "Conducía demasiado rápido.",
    "answer": "too, overly",
    "answerDetails": "He was driving too fast."
  },
  {
    "id": 538,
    "question": "atención",
    "questionDetails": "Prestar atención a algo/alguien.",
    "answer": "attention, care, service",
    "answerDetails": "To pay attention to something/somebody."
  },
  {
    "id": 539,
    "question": "mire",
    "questionDetails": "Y mire lo que le pasó.",
    "answer": "look, watch",
    "answerDetails": "Look what happened to him."
  },
  {
    "id": 540,
    "question": "vámonos",
    "questionDetails": "Dejemos el resto y vámonos.",
    "answer": "go",
    "answerDetails": "We should abandon the rest and go."
  },
  {
    "id": 541,
    "question": "posible",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando/donde sea posible.",
    "answer": "possible, potential",
    "answerDetails": "Whenever/wherever possible."
  },
  {
    "id": 542,
    "question": "par",
    "questionDetails": "La baronesa es un par que vive a poca distancia de la Casa de los Lores.",
    "answer": "peer",
    "answerDetails": "The Baroness is a peer living within walking distance of the House of Lords."
  },
  {
    "id": 543,
    "question": "hombres",
    "questionDetails": "Los hombres están pidiendo más que antes.",
    "answer": "men, Mens, guys",
    "answerDetails": "The men’s asking for more than they did before."
  },
  {
    "id": 544,
    "question": "permiso",
    "questionDetails": "Dar a alguien permiso para hacer algo.",
    "answer": "permission, leave, license",
    "answerDetails": "To give somebody permission to do something."
  },
  {
    "id": 545,
    "question": "matar",
    "questionDetails": "Sabía que me iba a matar.",
    "answer": "kill",
    "answerDetails": "I knew he would kill me."
  },
  {
    "id": 546,
    "question": "muerte",
    "questionDetails": "Incluso en la muerte, ella era hermosa.",
    "answer": "death, killing",
    "answerDetails": "Even in death, she was beautiful."
  },
  {
    "id": 547,
    "question": "mala",
    "questionDetails": "Tuve la misma mala sensación antes de esa operación también.",
    "answer": "bad, poor, ill",
    "answerDetails": "I had the same bad feeling before that op too."
  },
  {
    "id": 548,
    "question": "estuve",
    "questionDetails": "Yo no estuve nunca en esa escalera.",
    "answer": "was, stayed",
    "answerDetails": "I was never in that stairwell."
  },
  {
    "id": 549,
    "question": "joven",
    "questionDetails": "Espero que no sea demasiado joven.",
    "answer": "young, young man, youth",
    "answerDetails": "Hope she’s not too young for you."
  },
  {
    "id": 550,
    "question": "toca",
    "answer": "he plays"
  },
  {
    "id": 551,
    "question": "tuvo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Tuvo una reunión esta mañana?-No, fue cancelada.",
    "answer": "did you have",
    "answerDetails": "Did you have a meeting this morning?-No, it was cancelled."
  },
  {
    "id": 552,
    "question": "viaje",
    "questionDetails": "Un viaje en tren/avión/barco.",
    "answer": "journey, ride, voyage",
    "answerDetails": "A train/plane/boat journey."
  },
  {
    "id": 553,
    "question": "dejo",
    "questionDetails": "Abro la puerta y dejo la bandeja.",
    "answer": "leave, let",
    "answerDetails": "I open the door and leave the tray."
  },
  {
    "id": 554,
    "question": "entender",
    "questionDetails": "Para usted es un hombre que puede entender.",
    "answer": "understand",
    "answerDetails": "For you are a man that can understand."
  },
  {
    "id": 555,
    "question": "e",
    "questionDetails": "El era rico e inteligente.",
    "answer": "and",
    "answerDetails": "He was rich and smart."
  },
  {
    "id": 556,
    "question": "siete",
    "questionDetails": "Animales fueron ofrecidos para el sacrificio en sietes.",
    "answer": "seven",
    "answerDetails": "Animals were offered for sacrifice in sevens."
  },
  {
    "id": 557,
    "question": "adiós",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Adiós! Te veo la semana que viene.",
    "answer": "goodbye",
    "answerDetails": "Goodbye! See you next week."
  },
  {
    "id": 558,
    "question": "foto",
    "questionDetails": "Álbu M de fotos.",
    "answer": "photo, picture, shot",
    "answerDetails": "Photo album."
  },
  {
    "id": 559,
    "question": "dijeron",
    "questionDetails": "Dijeron que vendrían, pero después cambiaron de idea.",
    "answer": "they said, they told, you told",
    "answerDetails": "They said they would come, but then they changed their minds."
  },
  {
    "id": 560,
    "question": "dan",
    "questionDetails": "Yo soy uno de los tantos que le dan información.",
    "answer": "give",
    "answerDetails": "I am one of many who give him information."
  },
  {
    "id": 561,
    "question": "solamente",
    "questionDetails": "Solamente soy un asistente. Mi jefe toma esas decisiones.",
    "answer": "only, alone, solely",
    "answerDetails": "I’m only an assistant. My boss makes those decisions."
  },
  {
    "id": 562,
    "question": "necesita",
    "questionDetails": "¿Necesita algo más, señor?",
    "answer": "do you need, it needs",
    "answerDetails": "Do you need anything else, sir?"
  },
  {
    "id": 563,
    "question": "pagar",
    "questionDetails": "Se empeñó en pagarlo de su propio dinero or costeárselo él mismo.",
    "answer": "pay",
    "answerDetails": "He insisted on paying his way."
  },
  {
    "id": 564,
    "question": "salió",
    "answer": "Left"
  },
  {
    "id": 565,
    "question": "viejo",
    "questionDetails": "Se quejó de ser viejo más allá de sus años.",
    "answer": "old, ancient",
    "answerDetails": "He complained of being old beyond his years."
  },
  {
    "id": 566,
    "question": "viendo",
    "questionDetails": "Ya deberíamos estar viendo estrellas.",
    "answer": "seeing, watching, viewing",
    "answerDetails": "We should be seeing stars by now."
  },
  {
    "id": 567,
    "question": "morir",
    "questionDetails": "Morir de las heridas recibidas.",
    "answer": "die",
    "answerDetails": "To die from or of one’s wounds."
  },
  {
    "id": 568,
    "question": "imposible",
    "questionDetails": "Es imposible saber cuándo terminaremos.",
    "answer": "impossible, difficult",
    "answerDetails": "It’s impossible to say when we’ll finish."
  },
  {
    "id": 569,
    "question": "hiciste",
    "questionDetails": "¿Hiciste bien en el examen?",
    "answer": "did you do, you made it, you did it",
    "answerDetails": "Did you do well on your test?"
  },
  {
    "id": 570,
    "question": "estuvo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Ayer estuvo soleado?",
    "answer": "was it",
    "answerDetails": "Was it sunny yesterday?"
  },
  {
    "id": 571,
    "question": "déjame",
    "questionDetails": "¿Tienen otros ejemplares de este libro?-No Estoy seguro. Déjame ver.",
    "answer": "let me",
    "answerDetails": "Do you have any more copies of this book?-I’m not sure. Let me check."
  },
  {
    "id": 572,
    "question": "vayas",
    "questionDetails": "No vayas a salir así a la calle.",
    "answer": "go, ‘re going",
    "answerDetails": "Do not go out into the street looking so."
  },
  {
    "id": 573,
    "question": "vive",
    "answer": "Lives"
  },
  {
    "id": 574,
    "question": "fiesta",
    "questionDetails": "Voy a celebrar los 30 con una fiesta.",
    "answer": "party, feast, festival",
    "answerDetails": "I’m going to have a party for my 30th birthday."
  },
  {
    "id": 575,
    "question": "quiera",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando usted quiera que esto termine.",
    "answer": "want, pleases, wish",
    "answerDetails": "When you want this to stop."
  },
  {
    "id": 576,
    "question": "edad",
    "questionDetails": "Para esa edad, están muy metidos en el juego.",
    "answer": "age",
    "answerDetails": "By that age, they’re deep in the game."
  },
  {
    "id": 577,
    "question": "adentro",
    "questionDetails": "Dejé algo aquí adentro.",
    "answer": "in, inside",
    "answerDetails": "I left something in here."
  },
  {
    "id": 578,
    "question": "comida",
    "questionDetails": "El desayuno es la comida más importante del día.",
    "answer": "meal, lunch",
    "answerDetails": "Breakfast is the most important meal of the Day."
  },
  {
    "id": 579,
    "question": "nuestras",
    "questionDetails": "Es muy difícil coordinar nuestras actividades.",
    "answer": "our",
    "answerDetails": "Coordinating our schedules is difficult."
  },
  {
    "id": 580,
    "question": "policía",
    "questionDetails": "El policía me puso una multa por exceso de velocidad.",
    "answer": "officer, policeman",
    "answerDetails": "The officer issued me a speeding fine."
  },
  {
    "id": 581,
    "question": "bonito",
    "questionDetails": "El vestido es elegante y bonito.",
    "answer": "beautiful, lovely",
    "answerDetails": "The dress is elegant and beautiful."
  },
  {
    "id": 582,
    "question": "piensa",
    "questionDetails": "Piensa mucho en sus opciones antes de tomar una decisión.",
    "answer": "he thinks, do you think",
    "answerDetails": "He thinks a lot about his options before making a decision."
  },
  {
    "id": 583,
    "question": "boca",
    "questionDetails": "Pensó que Francis era toda la boca.",
    "answer": "mouth",
    "answerDetails": "He thought Francis was all mouth."
  },
  {
    "id": 584,
    "question": "traje",
    "questionDetails": "Todos los miembros del equipo llevaron trajes a juego para la ceremonia.",
    "answer": "suit, costume, clothes",
    "answerDetails": "All of the team members wore matching suits to the ceremony."
  },
  {
    "id": 585,
    "question": "querer",
    "answer": "To want"
  },
  {
    "id": 586,
    "question": "jugar",
    "questionDetails": "Jugar por or con dinero.",
    "answer": "play",
    "answerDetails": "To play for money."
  },
  {
    "id": 587,
    "question": "duro",
    "questionDetails": "El cordero estaba duro y soso.",
    "answer": "tough, rough",
    "answerDetails": "The Lamb was tough and flavorless."
  },
  {
    "id": 588,
    "question": "conocer",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero conocer el sudeste asiático este verano.",
    "answer": "to go to",
    "answerDetails": "I want to go to Southeast Asia this summer."
  },
  {
    "id": 589,
    "question": "pido",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo le pido que saque las conclusiones adecuadas.",
    "answer": "ask, beg, urge",
    "answerDetails": "I only ask that you draw the proper conclusions."
  },
  {
    "id": 590,
    "question": "vuelve",
    "questionDetails": "Dile a Rolando que fui a la tienda si vuelve.",
    "answer": "he comes back, be back",
    "answerDetails": "Tell Rolando that I went to the store if he comes back."
  },
  {
    "id": 591,
    "question": "juro",
    "answer": "i promise"
  },
  {
    "id": 592,
    "question": "ciudad",
    "questionDetails": "El personal estaba en la agitación-que era la ciudad pánico.",
    "answer": "city",
    "answerDetails": "The staff were in turmoil—it was Panic City."
  },
  {
    "id": 593,
    "question": "decirle",
    "questionDetails": "TIenes que decirle que ya no lo amas.",
    "answer": "tell him",
    "answerDetails": "You need to tell him that you don’t love him anymore."
  },
  {
    "id": 594,
    "question": "aún",
    "questionDetails": "Codiciaba aún más poder.",
    "answer": "still, yet, even",
    "answerDetails": "He lusted after still greater power."
  },
  {
    "id": 595,
    "question": "salud",
    "questionDetails": "La fábrica presenta un peligro para la salud pública.",
    "answer": "health",
    "answerDetails": "The factory poses a public health risk."
  },
  {
    "id": 596,
    "question": "malo",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Eres tan malo! ¡ Te pasas el día criticándome!.",
    "answer": "mean",
    "answerDetails": "You’re so mean! All you ever do is criticize me!."
  },
  {
    "id": 597,
    "question": "debería",
    "questionDetails": "¿Reiniciaste el ordenador? Debería funcionar ahora.",
    "answer": "it should, you ought to",
    "answerDetails": "Did you restart the computer? It should work now."
  },
  {
    "id": 598,
    "question": "conoce",
    "questionDetails": "No sé quién es Fernando.-Qué raro. Él dice que lo conoce a usted.",
    "answer": "he knows you, he meets, you know him",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t know who Fernando is.-That’s weird. He says he knows you."
  },
  {
    "id": 599,
    "question": "chica",
    "questionDetails": "La chica que trabaja para nosotros de niñera tiene 16 años.",
    "answer": "girl, chick, gal",
    "answerDetails": "The girl who babysits for us is 16 years old."
  },
  {
    "id": 600,
    "question": "afuera",
    "questionDetails": "No me gusta dormir afuera. Siempre me pican los mosquitos.",
    "answer": "outdoors",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t like to sleep outdoors. I always get bitten by mosquitos."
  },
  {
    "id": 601,
    "question": "situación",
    "questionDetails": "La situación de la ciudad es agradable.",
    "answer": "situation",
    "answerDetails": "The situation of the town is pleasant."
  },
  {
    "id": 602,
    "question": "ropa",
    "questionDetails": "Las víctimas del terremoto necesitan comida, ropa y frazadas.",
    "answer": "clothing, wear, apparel",
    "answerDetails": "The earthquake victims are in need of food, clothing, and blankets."
  },
  {
    "id": 603,
    "question": "tierra",
    "questionDetails": "Mi familia había trabajado la tierra durante muchos años.",
    "answer": "land, ground, soil",
    "answerDetails": "My family had worked the land for many years."
  },
  {
    "id": 604,
    "question": "alto",
    "questionDetails": "Hay que tomar un ascensor especial para subir a lo alto del edificio.",
    "answer": "top, upper, height",
    "answerDetails": "One must take a special elevator to reach the top of the building."
  },
  {
    "id": 605,
    "question": "supuesto",
    "questionDetails": "Tu idea se basa en el supuesto erróneo de que la gente se comporta de forma racional.",
    "answer": "assumption",
    "answerDetails": "Your idea is based on the erroneous assumption that people behave rationally."
  },
  {
    "id": 606,
    "question": "libre",
    "questionDetails": "El holandés libre, el pulimento libre, y las flotas noruegas libres.",
    "answer": "free, available, spare",
    "answerDetails": "The Free Dutch, Free Polish, and Free Norwegian fleets."
  },
  {
    "id": 607,
    "question": "algunos",
    "questionDetails": "Algunos individuos pueden recuperarse sin necesitar medicamentos.",
    "answer": "some",
    "answerDetails": "Some individuals may recover on their own without medication."
  },
  {
    "id": 608,
    "question": "segura",
    "questionDetails": "No estaria tan segura.",
    "answer": "sure, safe, secure",
    "answerDetails": "Do not be so sure."
  },
  {
    "id": 609,
    "question": "necesitamos",
    "questionDetails": "Necesitamos su ayuda para solucionar un problema.",
    "answer": "we need",
    "answerDetails": "We need your help to solve an issue."
  },
  {
    "id": 610,
    "question": "sangre",
    "questionDetails": "Sangre por debajo de la puerta.",
    "answer": "blood",
    "answerDetails": "Blood under the door."
  },
  {
    "id": 611,
    "question": "habrá",
    "questionDetails": "Habrá un concierto en la plaza esta noche.",
    "answer": "there will be",
    "answerDetails": "There will be a concert in the plaza tonight."
  },
  {
    "id": 612,
    "question": "trata",
    "questionDetails": "Trata de insert arte.",
    "answer": "try",
    "answerDetails": "Try to insert yourself."
  },
  {
    "id": 613,
    "question": "frente",
    "questionDetails": "Rápidamente se volvió la cabeza para enfrentar el frente.",
    "answer": "front, against, brow",
    "answerDetails": "She quickly turned her head to face the front."
  },
  {
    "id": 614,
    "question": "cuarto",
    "questionDetails": "Que no podía hacer nada mejor que terminar cuarto.",
    "answer": "fourth, quarter",
    "answerDetails": "He could do no better than finish fourth."
  },
  {
    "id": 615,
    "question": "escuchar",
    "questionDetails": "Le dije una y otra vez, pero ella no quiso escuchar.",
    "answer": "listen, hear",
    "answerDetails": "I told her over and over again, but she wouldn’t listen."
  },
  {
    "id": 616,
    "question": "hermana",
    "questionDetails": "Y a ver a mi hermana.",
    "answer": "sister",
    "answerDetails": "And to see my sister."
  },
  {
    "id": 617,
    "question": "encanta",
    "questionDetails": "Me encanta esta gente.",
    "answer": "love, adore",
    "answerDetails": "I love this crowd."
  },
  {
    "id": 618,
    "question": "vio",
    "questionDetails": "Estoy segura de que me vio, pero fingió no darse cuenta.",
    "answer": "he saw, saw him, he watched",
    "answerDetails": "I’m sure he saw me, but pretended not to notice me."
  },
  {
    "id": 619,
    "question": "especial",
    "questionDetails": "Gracias por hacer de mi cumpleaños un día muy especial.",
    "answer": "special, particular",
    "answerDetails": "Thank you for making my birthday a very special Day."
  },
  {
    "id": 620,
    "question": "resto",
    "questionDetails": "Mi intención es comer un poco del pastel ahora y dejar el resto para esta noche.",
    "answer": "rest, remainder",
    "answerDetails": "I plan to eat some of the cake and leave the rest for tonight."
  },
  {
    "id": 621,
    "question": "principio",
    "questionDetails": "Es un hombre íntegro que jamás traicionó sus principios.",
    "answer": "principle, beginning, start",
    "answerDetails": "He is an upright man who has never betrayed his principles."
  },
  {
    "id": 622,
    "question": "media",
    "questionDetails": "De media, alrededor de 2, 000 personas asisten a esos mítines.",
    "answer": "average, half hour, mean",
    "answerDetails": "On average, about 2,000 people attend those meetings."
  },
  {
    "id": 623,
    "question": "amiga",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Claro que conozco a Lucy! ¡ Es una amiga de toda la vida!.",
    "answer": "pal",
    "answerDetails": "Of course I know Lucy! She’s one of my old pals!."
  },
  {
    "id": 624,
    "question": "verte",
    "questionDetails": "Pueden verte llegar a una milla.",
    "answer": "seeyou, see",
    "answerDetails": "They can seeyou coming from a mile away."
  },
  {
    "id": 625,
    "question": "puso",
    "answer": "Put"
  },
  {
    "id": 626,
    "question": "querido",
    "questionDetails": "Querido Tom: ¿Cómo están tus hijos?",
    "answer": "dear",
    "answerDetails": "Dear Tom, How are the children?"
  },
  {
    "id": 627,
    "question": "chicos",
    "questionDetails": "Y eso hablando de los chicos.",
    "answer": "boys",
    "answerDetails": "And that’s just the boys."
  },
  {
    "id": 628,
    "question": "recuerdo",
    "questionDetails": "No tengo ningún recuerdo de esa noche.",
    "answer": "recall, souvenir, remembrance",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t have any recall from that night."
  },
  {
    "id": 629,
    "question": "teníamos",
    "questionDetails": "Teníamos muchas alergias cuando éramos pequeños.",
    "answer": "we had",
    "answerDetails": "We had a lot of allergies when we were little."
  },
  {
    "id": 630,
    "question": "encuentro",
    "questionDetails": "Nuestro Agente Secreto en Berlín no acudió al encuentro acostumbrado.",
    "answer": "rendezvous",
    "answerDetails": "Our secret agent in Berlin missed the usual rendezvous."
  },
  {
    "id": 631,
    "question": "pensaba",
    "answer": "i was thinking"
  },
  {
    "id": 632,
    "question": "vea",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero que la gente lo vea.",
    "answer": "see, watch, look",
    "answerDetails": "I want people to see that."
  },
  {
    "id": 633,
    "question": "jefe",
    "questionDetails": "El jefe de la policía.",
    "answer": "chief",
    "answerDetails": "The chief of police."
  },
  {
    "id": 634,
    "question": "vete",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Vete, niño!.",
    "answer": "go away, get gone",
    "answerDetails": "Go away, kid!."
  },
  {
    "id": 635,
    "question": "cama",
    "questionDetails": "Estaba en la cama con la mafia.",
    "answer": "bed, bunk",
    "answerDetails": "He was in bed with the Mob."
  },
  {
    "id": 636,
    "question": "venido",
    "questionDetails": "Pude haber venido antes pero tu ayuno ayuda.",
    "answer": "come",
    "answerDetails": "I could have come earlier but your fast has helped."
  },
  {
    "id": 637,
    "question": "comprar",
    "questionDetails": "Comprar algo a Or para alguien.",
    "answer": "buy, shop",
    "answerDetails": "To buy somebody something, to buy something for somebody."
  },
  {
    "id": 638,
    "question": "pongo",
    "questionDetails": "Me siento a mi escritorio y pongo comas.",
    "answer": "put, wear",
    "answerDetails": "I sit at my desk and put commas in."
  },
  {
    "id": 639,
    "question": "siguiente",
    "questionDetails": "Las siguientes son frases gramaticalmente correctas.",
    "answer": "following",
    "answerDetails": "The following are both grammatically correct sentences."
  },
  {
    "id": 640,
    "question": "niña",
    "questionDetails": "¿Ya saben el sexo del bebé?-Es una niña.",
    "answer": "she",
    "answerDetails": "Have you found out the sex of the baby?-It’s a she."
  },
  {
    "id": 641,
    "question": "terminar",
    "questionDetails": "No sé cómo terminar esta relación.",
    "answer": "end, complete, conclude",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t know how to end this relationship."
  },
  {
    "id": 642,
    "question": "acabo",
    "questionDetails": "A veces comienzo a reírme cuando acabo y se asusta mi pareja.",
    "answer": "i am coming",
    "answerDetails": "Sometimes I start laughing when I am coming and my partner freaks out."
  },
  {
    "id": 643,
    "question": "hacia",
    "questionDetails": "Él era cálido y tierno hacia su.",
    "answer": "towards, around, at",
    "answerDetails": "He was warm and tender towards her."
  },
  {
    "id": 644,
    "question": "delante",
    "questionDetails": "Pero no me preocupa delante de ti.",
    "answer": "before",
    "answerDetails": "But before you worry me."
  },
  {
    "id": 645,
    "question": "hubo",
    "answer": "there were"
  },
  {
    "id": 646,
    "question": "uy",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Uy! ¿Pero qué haces tú aquí?",
    "answer": "whoa",
    "answerDetails": "Whoa! But what are you doing here?"
  },
  {
    "id": 647,
    "question": "vine",
    "answer": "Came"
  },
  {
    "id": 648,
    "question": "jamás",
    "questionDetails": "Su cuerpo jamás fue recuperado.",
    "answer": "never, ever",
    "answerDetails": "His body was never recovered."
  },
  {
    "id": 649,
    "question": "voz",
    "questionDetails": "Levantar/bajar la voz.",
    "answer": "voice, word",
    "answerDetails": "To raise/lower one’s voice."
  },
  {
    "id": 650,
    "question": "hicieron",
    "questionDetails": "Se nos robaron los pasaportes cuando estábamos de viaje.-¿Qué hicieron? ¿Como volvieron?",
    "answer": "did you do",
    "answerDetails": "Our passports were stolen while traveling.-What did you do? How did you get home?"
  },
  {
    "id": 651,
    "question": "detrás",
    "questionDetails": "La casa tiene un jardín grande detrás.",
    "answer": "back, behind, in tow",
    "answerDetails": "The house’s got a large garden at the back."
  },
  {
    "id": 652,
    "question": "venía",
    "questionDetails": "Sí, recuerdo a Sandra. Venía a mi oficina para citas muy frecuentemente.",
    "answer": "she came",
    "answerDetails": "Yes, I remember Sandra. She came to my office for appointments very frequently."
  },
  {
    "id": 653,
    "question": "pelo",
    "questionDetails": "Tienes que recogerte el pelo para trabajar en mi cocina.",
    "answer": "hair",
    "answerDetails": "You have to put your hair up to work in my kitchen."
  },
  {
    "id": 654,
    "question": "quedan",
    "questionDetails": "Quedan dos criaturas, mi señor.",
    "answer": "remain, left, are",
    "answerDetails": "Two creatures remain, my lord."
  },
  {
    "id": 655,
    "question": "dé",
    "questionDetails": "Entonces, dé me uno de éstos.",
    "answer": "give",
    "answerDetails": "Then give me one of these."
  },
  {
    "id": 656,
    "question": "derecho",
    "questionDetails": "No siempre ha permanecido en el lado derecho de la ley.",
    "answer": "right",
    "answerDetails": "He hasn’t always remained on the right side of the law."
  },
  {
    "id": 657,
    "question": "sorpresa",
    "questionDetails": "Te confiamos con el cuidado de Jason y sorpresa sorpresa, que hacer un desastre de la misma.",
    "answer": "surprise",
    "answerDetails": "We entrust you with Jason’s care and, surprise surprise, you make a mess of it."
  },
  {
    "id": 658,
    "question": "acabó",
    "questionDetails": "Seguiste dormida en mis brazos hasta que acabó el partido.",
    "answer": "ended, finished, ended up",
    "answerDetails": "You stayed asleep in my arms till the game ended."
  },
  {
    "id": 659,
    "question": "durante",
    "questionDetails": "Las mujeres deben evitar el alcohol durante el embarazo.",
    "answer": "during, over, for",
    "answerDetails": "Women should avoid alcohol during pregnancy."
  },
  {
    "id": 660,
    "question": "cuántos",
    "answer": "how many"
  },
  {
    "id": 661,
    "question": "realmente",
    "questionDetails": "Realmente, Marjorie, ¡ Salta a las conclusiones!.",
    "answer": "really, actually, truly",
    "answerDetails": "Really, Marjorie, you do jump to conclusions!."
  },
  {
    "id": 662,
    "question": "mensaje",
    "questionDetails": "Captó el mensaje y se mantuvo alejado.",
    "answer": "message",
    "answerDetails": "He got the message and stayed away."
  },
  {
    "id": 663,
    "question": "futuro",
    "questionDetails": "Había decidido que no había futuro en la pandilla.",
    "answer": "future",
    "answerDetails": "He’d decided that there was no future in the gang."
  },
  {
    "id": 664,
    "question": "don",
    "questionDetails": "Tener un don para las matemáticas.",
    "answer": "gift, mr, knack",
    "answerDetails": "To have a gift for mathematics."
  },
  {
    "id": 665,
    "question": "cuento",
    "questionDetails": "No me dormiré hasta que no me cuentes un cuento.",
    "answer": "story",
    "answerDetails": "I won’t go to sleep unless you tell me a story."
  },
  {
    "id": 666,
    "question": "música",
    "questionDetails": "Poner música a la letra.",
    "answer": "music",
    "answerDetails": "To set words to music."
  },
  {
    "id": 667,
    "question": "increíble",
    "questionDetails": "Un número increíble de personas registradas.",
    "answer": "amazing, incredible",
    "answerDetails": "An amazing number of people registered."
  },
  {
    "id": 668,
    "question": "hablo",
    "questionDetails": "Yo hablo su idioma, por así decirlo.",
    "answer": "speak, talk",
    "answerDetails": "I speak their language, you might say."
  },
  {
    "id": 669,
    "question": "personal",
    "questionDetails": "El personal de la oficina trabaja mucho.",
    "answer": "staff, personnel",
    "answerDetails": "The staff of the office works hard."
  },
  {
    "id": 670,
    "question": "vuelvo",
    "answer": "I"
  },
  {
    "id": 671,
    "question": "perdido",
    "questionDetails": "Dar algo/a alguien por perdido (a).",
    "answer": "lost",
    "answerDetails": "To give something/somebody up for lost."
  },
  {
    "id": 672,
    "question": "loca",
    "questionDetails": "Ya sé que está loca de remate.",
    "answer": "crazy",
    "answerDetails": "I know you’re crazy auction."
  },
  {
    "id": 673,
    "question": "deje",
    "answer": "i left"
  },
  {
    "id": 674,
    "question": "novia",
    "questionDetails": "Tenía una novia y un amigo.",
    "answer": "sweetheart",
    "answerDetails": "I had a sweetheart and a friend."
  },
  {
    "id": 675,
    "question": "fuiste",
    "questionDetails": "La escuela fue interesante ayer. ¿Fuiste?",
    "answer": "did you go",
    "answerDetails": "School was interesting yesterday. Did you go?"
  },
  {
    "id": 676,
    "question": "clase",
    "questionDetails": "Basta ver la forma que tiene de sujetar el cigarro para darse cuenta de que tiene clase.",
    "answer": "class",
    "answerDetails": "Just by looking at the way she holds her cigarette, you can tell she’s got class."
  },
  {
    "id": 677,
    "question": "exactamente",
    "questionDetails": "¿Qué es exactamente lo que busca?",
    "answer": "exactly, precisely",
    "answerDetails": "What exactly are you looking for?"
  },
  {
    "id": 678,
    "question": "tuya",
    "questionDetails": "La responsabilidad no es nuestra sino tuya.",
    "answer": "thine",
    "answerDetails": "The responsibility is not ours but thine."
  },
  {
    "id": 679,
    "question": "mejores",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo algunos de los mejores doctores del mundo.",
    "answer": "best, finest, top",
    "answerDetails": "I have some of the best doctors in the world."
  },
  {
    "id": 680,
    "question": "chico",
    "questionDetails": "Yo era el chico nuevo en la oficina.",
    "answer": "boy",
    "answerDetails": "I was the new boy at the office."
  },
  {
    "id": 681,
    "question": "empieza",
    "questionDetails": "Entonces Laura Alza la mano. “Yo creo,” empieza a decir.",
    "answer": "she begins, he starts",
    "answerDetails": "Then Laura raises her hand. “I think,” she begins to say."
  },
  {
    "id": 682,
    "question": "marido",
    "questionDetails": "Mi marido me regaló un precioso ramo de rosas.",
    "answer": "husband",
    "answerDetails": "My husband gave me a lovely bouquet of roses."
  },
  {
    "id": 683,
    "question": "capaz",
    "questionDetails": "Parecía entusiasta y capaz.",
    "answer": "capable",
    "answerDetails": "She looked enthusiastic and capable."
  },
  {
    "id": 684,
    "question": "perfectamente",
    "questionDetails": "Harry compró una billetera europea para que los billetes de euro encajaran perfectamente en Ella.",
    "answer": "neatly",
    "answerDetails": "Harry bought a European wallet so that the euro bills would fit neatly into it."
  },
  {
    "id": 685,
    "question": "tenías",
    "questionDetails": "Tú tenías mi anillo.",
    "answer": "had",
    "answerDetails": "You had my ring."
  },
  {
    "id": 686,
    "question": "gustan",
    "answer": "Like"
  },
  {
    "id": 687,
    "question": "verlo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Vas a ir al juego?-No, voy a verlo en la Televisión.",
    "answer": "watch it",
    "answerDetails": "Are you going to the game?-No, I’m going to watch it on television."
  },
  {
    "id": 688,
    "question": "significa",
    "questionDetails": "¿Ves esta palabra? Significa “comida” en alemán.",
    "answer": "it means",
    "answerDetails": "See this word? It means “food” in German."
  },
  {
    "id": 689,
    "question": "sirve",
    "questionDetails": "Carla es una tenista formidable. Sirve la pelota con tanta fuerza que pocos la pueden devolver.",
    "answer": "she serves, will do",
    "answerDetails": "Carla is a formidable tennis player. She serves the ball so hard that few can return it."
  },
  {
    "id": 690,
    "question": "baja",
    "questionDetails": "El jefe estuvo de baja toda la semana.",
    "answer": "sick leave",
    "answerDetails": "The boss was on sick leave the whole week."
  },
  {
    "id": 691,
    "question": "padres",
    "questionDetails": "Mis padres me dijeron que dejara de ir.",
    "answer": "parents, fathers, dads",
    "answerDetails": "My parents told me to stop going."
  },
  {
    "id": 692,
    "question": "regalo",
    "questionDetails": "El regalo de su madre de una pluma.",
    "answer": "gift, present, giveaway",
    "answerDetails": "His mother’s gift of a pen."
  },
  {
    "id": 693,
    "question": "grandes",
    "questionDetails": "Esos son demasiado grandes.",
    "answer": "large, big, great",
    "answerDetails": "Those are much too large."
  },
  {
    "id": 694,
    "question": "empezó",
    "questionDetails": "Empezó a trabajar a las 8 am hoy.",
    "answer": "she started, she began",
    "answerDetails": "She started working at 8 A.M. today."
  },
  {
    "id": 695,
    "question": "ibas",
    "questionDetails": "Pensé que nunca ibas a.",
    "answer": "were, IBA",
    "answerDetails": "I thought you were never."
  },
  {
    "id": 696,
    "question": "suficiente",
    "questionDetails": "Usted no es lo suficientemente grande para el baloncesto.",
    "answer": "enough, sufficient",
    "answerDetails": "You’re not big enough for basketball."
  },
  {
    "id": 697,
    "question": "llegado",
    "questionDetails": "Ese momento ha llegado.",
    "answer": "arrived, come, reached",
    "answerDetails": "That moment has now arrived."
  },
  {
    "id": 698,
    "question": "juego",
    "questionDetails": "Cada hogar necesita un juego de herramientas.",
    "answer": "set, gaming, stake",
    "answerDetails": "Every home needs a set of tools."
  },
  {
    "id": 699,
    "question": "dejé",
    "questionDetails": "Te dejé un poco de dinero.",
    "answer": "left, stopped, quit",
    "answerDetails": "I left you a few bucks."
  },
  {
    "id": 700,
    "question": "fondo",
    "questionDetails": "Fondos mpl.",
    "answer": "fund, bottom",
    "answerDetails": "Funds."
  },
  {
    "id": 701,
    "question": "tío",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Cómo mola, tío!.",
    "answer": "man, dude, guy",
    "answerDetails": "That’s cool, man!."
  },
  {
    "id": 702,
    "question": "querías",
    "questionDetails": "¿Por qué me estás regalando tu reloj viejo?-Dijiste que lo querías.",
    "answer": "you wanted it",
    "answerDetails": "Why are you giving me your old watch?-You said you wanted it."
  },
  {
    "id": 703,
    "question": "hablas",
    "questionDetails": "Me gusta escucharte cuando hablas.",
    "answer": "talk, speak",
    "answerDetails": "I like listening to your talk."
  },
  {
    "id": 704,
    "question": "murió",
    "questionDetails": "¿Qué le pasó al monstruo?-Murió debido a las heridas.",
    "answer": "it died",
    "answerDetails": "What happened to the monster?-It died due to the wounds."
  },
  {
    "id": 705,
    "question": "trae",
    "questionDetails": "¿Por qué no te agrada Ryan?-Trae caos y problemas.",
    "answer": "he brings, it brings",
    "answerDetails": "Why don’t you like Ryan?-He brings chaos and trouble."
  },
  {
    "id": 706,
    "question": "dejado",
    "questionDetails": "He dejado algo de cena para tí en la nevera.",
    "answer": "left, stopped, ceased",
    "answerDetails": "I left some dinner for you in the fridge."
  },
  {
    "id": 707,
    "question": "cariño",
    "questionDetails": "Te extraño, cariño.",
    "answer": "honey, sweetheart, baby",
    "answerDetails": "I miss you, honey."
  },
  {
    "id": 708,
    "question": "partir",
    "questionDetails": "Pensamos partir para el aeropuerto después del almuerzo.",
    "answer": "depart",
    "answerDetails": "We plan to depart for the airport after lunch."
  },
  {
    "id": 709,
    "question": "daño",
    "questionDetails": "El daño a su reputación fue considerable.",
    "answer": "damage, harm",
    "answerDetails": "The damage to his reputation was considerable."
  },
  {
    "id": 710,
    "question": "dando",
    "questionDetails": "Tratáre de aclarar lo que quiero decir dando una mejor explicación de mi proyecto.",
    "answer": "by giving",
    "answerDetails": "I will try to clarify what I mean by giving a better explanation of my project."
  },
  {
    "id": 711,
    "question": "basta",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Basta! No me gusta que me hagan cosquillas.",
    "answer": "stop that",
    "answerDetails": "Stop that! I don’t like being tickled."
  },
  {
    "id": 712,
    "question": "llegamos",
    "questionDetails": "¿Dónde está Lucille?-Llegamos a la fiesta juntas pero ahora no sé dónde está.",
    "answer": "we came",
    "answerDetails": "Where’s Lucille?-We came to the party together, but I don’t know where she is now."
  },
  {
    "id": 713,
    "question": "palabras",
    "questionDetails": "Quisiera decir unas palabras sobre nuestro amigo fallecido.",
    "answer": "some words, utterance",
    "answerDetails": "I would like to say some words about our departed friend."
  },
  {
    "id": 714,
    "question": "silencio",
    "questionDetails": "Sirenas perforar el silencio de la noche.",
    "answer": "silence, mute, hush",
    "answerDetails": "Sirens Pierce the silence of the night."
  },
  {
    "id": 715,
    "question": "montón",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo un montón que hacer hoy.",
    "answer": "lots, bunch, loads",
    "answerDetails": "I’ve got lots to do today."
  },
  {
    "id": 716,
    "question": "aire",
    "questionDetails": "El aire en la ciudad está contaminado.",
    "answer": "air",
    "answerDetails": "The air in the city is polluted."
  },
  {
    "id": 717,
    "question": "señores",
    "questionDetails": "Estos señores son cazadores de primera clase, amigo mío.",
    "answer": "gentlemen, lords, sirs",
    "answerDetails": "These gentlemen are fine hunters, my friend."
  },
  {
    "id": 718,
    "question": "relación",
    "questionDetails": "Hay una relación entre la privación de sueño y la cardiopatía.",
    "answer": "relationship, connection",
    "answerDetails": "There is a relationship between sleep deprivation and heart disease."
  },
  {
    "id": 719,
    "question": "cuanto",
    "questionDetails": "Pagas en base a cuantos escojas.",
    "answer": "how many, as many as",
    "answerDetails": "You pay depending on how many you choose."
  },
  {
    "id": 720,
    "question": "pueblo",
    "questionDetails": "Declaraciones previas al juicio hechas por los testigos del pueblo.",
    "answer": "people, town, country",
    "answerDetails": "Pre-trial statements made by the People’s witnesses."
  },
  {
    "id": 721,
    "question": "gana",
    "questionDetails": "La madre gana en lo duro.",
    "answer": "wins, earn, gains",
    "answerDetails": "The mother wins over the tough."
  },
  {
    "id": 722,
    "question": "tanta",
    "questionDetails": "Alguna gente tiene tanta suerte.",
    "answer": "so",
    "answerDetails": "Some people are so lucky."
  },
  {
    "id": 723,
    "question": "sentir",
    "questionDetails": "Con la primera helada, podían sentir un cambio en los días.",
    "answer": "sense",
    "answerDetails": "With the first frost, they could sense a change in the days."
  },
  {
    "id": 724,
    "question": "largo",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos un camino largo por delante para llegar a casa.",
    "answer": "long, length",
    "answerDetails": "We have a long way to go before we get home."
  },
  {
    "id": 725,
    "question": "algunas",
    "questionDetails": "Cosas que fueron cosas que son y algunas.",
    "answer": "some",
    "answerDetails": "Things that were things that are and some things."
  },
  {
    "id": 726,
    "question": "dile",
    "answer": "tell him"
  },
  {
    "id": 727,
    "question": "beso",
    "questionDetails": "Dar un beso a alguien.",
    "answer": "kiss",
    "answerDetails": "To give somebody a kiss."
  },
  {
    "id": 728,
    "question": "café",
    "questionDetails": "Tomé una taza de café.",
    "answer": "coffee",
    "answerDetails": "I had a cup of coffee."
  },
  {
    "id": 729,
    "question": "encontré",
    "questionDetails": "Después de un examen cuidadoso de los hechos, encontré algunas incoherencias.",
    "answer": "i found",
    "answerDetails": "After a close examination of the facts, I found some inconsistencies."
  },
  {
    "id": 730,
    "question": "escucha",
    "questionDetails": "La escucha es una destreza importante para trabajar en el servicio de atención al cliente.",
    "answer": "listening",
    "answerDetails": "Listening is an important skill for working in customer service."
  },
  {
    "id": 731,
    "question": "mes",
    "questionDetails": "Que era el final del mes.",
    "answer": "month",
    "answerDetails": "It was the end of the month."
  },
  {
    "id": 732,
    "question": "entra",
    "questionDetails": "Es el malvado de la obra. Se sabe porque la música cambia a una tonalidad menor cuando entra.",
    "answer": "he enters, please come in, does it fit",
    "answerDetails": "He’s the plays’ bad guy. You know because the music changes to a minor key when he enters."
  },
  {
    "id": 733,
    "question": "perro",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos que poner en el perro para Anne Marie.",
    "answer": "dog",
    "answerDetails": "We have to put on the dog for Anne Marie."
  },
  {
    "id": 734,
    "question": "hambre",
    "questionDetails": "Ella se desmayó con el hambre.",
    "answer": "hunger, starvation, famine",
    "answerDetails": "She was faint with Hunger."
  },
  {
    "id": 735,
    "question": "según",
    "questionDetails": "Según los términos del contrato, no puedes renunciar sin dar 2 semanas de aviso.",
    "answer": "under, on, according to",
    "answerDetails": "Under the terms of the contract, you cannot quit without giving two weeks notice."
  },
  {
    "id": 736,
    "question": "semanas",
    "questionDetails": "Se suele quitar en un par de semanas.",
    "answer": "weeks",
    "answerDetails": "It usually comes off in a couple of weeks."
  },
  {
    "id": 737,
    "question": "entiende",
    "questionDetails": "¿Entiende Mary El Español?-Sí, entiende el español.",
    "answer": "she understands, she is understanding, be understanding",
    "answerDetails": "Does Mary understand Spanish?-Yes, she understands Spanish."
  },
  {
    "id": 738,
    "question": "lista",
    "questionDetails": "Siempre hago una lista de las cosas que necesito antes de viajar.",
    "answer": "list, roster",
    "answerDetails": "I always make a list of things that I need before I travel."
  },
  {
    "id": 739,
    "question": "debo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Te debo dejar estudiar, o invitarte al cine?",
    "answer": "should i",
    "answerDetails": "Should I let you study, or invite you to the movies?"
  },
  {
    "id": 740,
    "question": "fotos",
    "questionDetails": "Ningún documento, ni fotos de la infancia.",
    "answer": "photos, pictures, pics",
    "answerDetails": "No records, no childhood photos."
  },
  {
    "id": 741,
    "question": "siente",
    "questionDetails": "Siente una patada en el costado y voltea para ver que su bebé se ha despertado.",
    "answer": "she feels, is sorry",
    "answerDetails": "She feels a kick in her side and turns around to see her baby has woken up."
  },
  {
    "id": 742,
    "question": "dolor",
    "questionDetails": "Sufre del dolor de una infancia difícil.",
    "answer": "pain, sorrow, suffering",
    "answerDetails": "She suffers from the pain of a difficult childhood."
  },
  {
    "id": 743,
    "question": "quedo",
    "questionDetails": "Me quedo cerca de casa.",
    "answer": "stay",
    "answerDetails": "I stay close to home."
  },
  {
    "id": 744,
    "question": "centro",
    "questionDetails": "Alexandra grita al hablar porque le gusta ser el centro de Atención.",
    "answer": "center, centre, middle",
    "answerDetails": "Alexandra shouts when she talks because she likes being the center of attention."
  },
  {
    "id": 745,
    "question": "íbamos",
    "answer": "Were"
  },
  {
    "id": 746,
    "question": "llamado",
    "questionDetails": "Cenamos en un restaurante llamado “Metropol”.",
    "answer": "called, named",
    "answerDetails": "We dined at a restaurant called “Metropol.”."
  },
  {
    "id": 747,
    "question": "segunda",
    "questionDetails": "La segunda, llegó tarde.",
    "answer": "second",
    "answerDetails": "The second time, he was late."
  },
  {
    "id": 748,
    "question": "frío",
    "questionDetails": "Dejamos frío detrás de un turno en la escalera.",
    "answer": "cold",
    "answerDetails": "We stopped cold behind a turn in the staircase."
  },
  {
    "id": 749,
    "question": "ajá",
    "questionDetails": "Habrá otro chico para mí, ajá.",
    "answer": "aha",
    "answerDetails": "There must be another one for me, aha."
  },
  {
    "id": 750,
    "question": "plan",
    "questionDetails": "El gobierno municipal ideó un plan para revitalizar el centro de la ciudad.",
    "answer": "scheme, programme",
    "answerDetails": "The city government developed a scheme to revitalize its downtown area."
  },
  {
    "id": 751,
    "question": "respeto",
    "questionDetails": "Es importante tener respeto por las opiniones de los demás aunque no estés de acuerdo.",
    "answer": "respect, regard",
    "answerDetails": "It’s important to have respect for other people’s opinions even if you don’t agree with them."
  },
  {
    "id": 752,
    "question": "muchísimo",
    "answer": "vastly"
  },
  {
    "id": 753,
    "question": "pobre",
    "questionDetails": "El pobre tipo en bicicleta.",
    "answer": "poor, meager, poor fellow",
    "answerDetails": "The poor guy on the bike."
  },
  {
    "id": 754,
    "question": "salga",
    "questionDetails": "Dejad que el cuerpo se exprese y que salga.",
    "answer": "exit, leave, quit",
    "answerDetails": "Let the body expression and exit."
  },
  {
    "id": 755,
    "question": "tocar",
    "questionDetails": "Estas pinturas son útiles para tocar áreas pequeñas en paredes o techos.",
    "answer": "touch",
    "answerDetails": "These paints are handy for touching up small areas on walls or ceilings."
  },
  {
    "id": 756,
    "question": "conoces",
    "questionDetails": "Claro que me conoces.",
    "answer": "know",
    "answerDetails": "Of course you know me."
  },
  {
    "id": 757,
    "question": "acuerdas",
    "questionDetails": "Hijo mío tú no te acuerdas de mí.",
    "answer": "remember, recall",
    "answerDetails": "My son you do not remember me."
  },
  {
    "id": 758,
    "question": "hicimos",
    "questionDetails": "Hicimos todo los que pudimos, pero se nos acabó el tiempo.",
    "answer": "we did",
    "answerDetails": "We did everything we could, but we ran out of time."
  },
  {
    "id": 759,
    "question": "existe",
    "questionDetails": "Existe en el universo.",
    "answer": "exists, there",
    "answerDetails": "And it exists in the universe."
  },
  {
    "id": 760,
    "question": "señorita",
    "questionDetails": "Buenas tardes, señorita. ¿Cómo le puedo ayudar?",
    "answer": "miss",
    "answerDetails": "Good afternoon, miss. How may I help you?"
  },
  {
    "id": 761,
    "question": "oh",
    "answer": "Oh, o, Ooh"
  },
  {
    "id": 762,
    "question": "tardes",
    "questionDetails": "Nunca bebes café por las tardes.",
    "answer": "afternoon, evening",
    "answerDetails": "You never drink coffee in the afternoon."
  },
  {
    "id": 763,
    "question": "sueño",
    "questionDetails": "Un sueño hecho realidad.",
    "answer": "dream, sleepy, slumber",
    "answerDetails": "A dream come true."
  },
  {
    "id": 764,
    "question": "quedado",
    "questionDetails": "Debería haberme quedado en coma.",
    "answer": "stayed, been, remained",
    "answerDetails": "I should have stayed in the coma."
  },
  {
    "id": 765,
    "question": "fuimos",
    "questionDetails": "¿Cómo llegaron a Londres?-Fuimos en el tren subterráneo de alta velocidad.",
    "answer": "we rode",
    "answerDetails": "How did you get to London?-We rode on the underground high-speed train."
  },
  {
    "id": 766,
    "question": "mitad",
    "questionDetails": "Él no es la mitad de un tonto, ya que pensaban.",
    "answer": "half, middle",
    "answerDetails": "He is not half such a fool as they thought."
  },
  {
    "id": 767,
    "question": "busca",
    "questionDetails": "Casey no puede encontrar un nuevo trabajo aunque busca uno cada día.",
    "answer": "he looks for, pursuit",
    "answerDetails": "Casey can’t find a new job even though he looks for one every Day."
  },
  {
    "id": 768,
    "question": "repente",
    "questionDetails": "Algunos llegan de repente, a grandes saltos.",
    "answer": "suddenly, sudden, abruptly",
    "answerDetails": "Some of them come suddenly, in big jumps."
  },
  {
    "id": 769,
    "question": "bonita",
    "questionDetails": "Su región es muy bonita.",
    "answer": "beautiful",
    "answerDetails": "Your land is very beautiful."
  },
  {
    "id": 770,
    "question": "ojalá",
    "questionDetails": "“Ojalá no tuviera que ser así”. “Si los deseos eran los caballos”, suspiró David.",
    "answer": "wish, hopefully",
    "answerDetails": "‘I wish it didn’t have to be that way.’ ‘If wishes were horses,’ David sighed."
  },
  {
    "id": 771,
    "question": "conseguir",
    "questionDetails": "Necesito todo el sueño que pueda conseguir.",
    "answer": "get, obtain",
    "answerDetails": "I need all the sleep I can get."
  },
  {
    "id": 772,
    "question": "vayan",
    "questionDetails": "Vayan a la puerta principal.",
    "answer": "go",
    "answerDetails": "You go over to the main gate."
  },
  {
    "id": 773,
    "question": "pude",
    "questionDetails": "Nunca pude conseguir un control sobre él.",
    "answer": "could",
    "answerDetails": "Never could get a grip on it."
  },
  {
    "id": 774,
    "question": "médico",
    "questionDetails": "El médico ya confirmó que estabas enfermo.",
    "answer": "doctor",
    "answerDetails": "The doctor already confirmed you were sick."
  },
  {
    "id": 775,
    "question": "tengas",
    "questionDetails": "Espero que tengas estómago.",
    "answer": "have",
    "answerDetails": "I hope you have a strong stomach."
  },
  {
    "id": 776,
    "question": "cuántas",
    "questionDetails": "Descubrí cuántas de estas cosas funcionan vía online.",
    "answer": "how much, many",
    "answerDetails": "I found out how much these things are going for online."
  },
  {
    "id": 777,
    "question": "abre",
    "answer": "Open"
  },
  {
    "id": 778,
    "question": "llamas",
    "questionDetails": "Lo que sigue es una botella en llamas.",
    "answer": "flaming, call, fire",
    "answerDetails": "The following is a flaming bottle."
  },
  {
    "id": 779,
    "question": "lleno",
    "questionDetails": "Estoy lleno a tope y no puedo comer postre.",
    "answer": "full, packed, teeming",
    "answerDetails": "I’m completely full and have no room for dessert."
  },
  {
    "id": 780,
    "question": "empezamos",
    "questionDetails": "Tenemos que terminar lo que empezamos.",
    "answer": "we started",
    "answerDetails": "We need to finish what we started."
  },
  {
    "id": 781,
    "question": "vieja",
    "questionDetails": "Esa es una vieja historia.",
    "answer": "old, old lady, old woman",
    "answerDetails": "That is an old story."
  },
  {
    "id": 782,
    "question": "seguridad",
    "questionDetails": "La seguridad emocional de ser la única persona especial que alguien más ama.",
    "answer": "security, safety",
    "answerDetails": "The emotional security of being the one special person that someone else loves."
  },
  {
    "id": 783,
    "question": "anoche",
    "questionDetails": "¿Qué hiciste anoche antes de acostarte?",
    "answer": "yesterday evening",
    "answerDetails": "What did you do yesterday evening before going to bed?"
  },
  {
    "id": 784,
    "question": "confianza",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo total confianza en tu capacidad para sacar el proyecto Adelante.",
    "answer": "trust",
    "answerDetails": "I have every trust in your ability to get the project off the Ground."
  },
  {
    "id": 785,
    "question": "duele",
    "questionDetails": "Cuando ves algo triste te duele el corazón.",
    "answer": "it hurts",
    "answerDetails": "When you witness something sad it hurts your heart."
  },
  {
    "id": 786,
    "question": "podido",
    "questionDetails": "Nunca me lo he podido permitir hasta ahora.",
    "answer": "could",
    "answerDetails": "Never could afford it till now."
  },
  {
    "id": 787,
    "question": "diferente",
    "questionDetails": "Las cosas son definitivamente diferentes de lo que eran hace un año.",
    "answer": "different, distinct",
    "answerDetails": "Things are definitely different than they were one year ago."
  },
  {
    "id": 788,
    "question": "mentira",
    "questionDetails": "Me dijo una mentira para que no la castigara.",
    "answer": "lie, bullshit",
    "answerDetails": "She told me a lie so that I wouldn’t punish her."
  },
  {
    "id": 789,
    "question": "seguimos",
    "questionDetails": "Medimos, nos muestran, seguimos adelante.",
    "answer": "we",
    "answerDetails": "We measure, we show it, we move on."
  },
  {
    "id": 790,
    "question": "pie",
    "questionDetails": "Es muy húmedo bajo el pie en lugares.",
    "answer": "foot, stand",
    "answerDetails": "It is very wet under foot in places."
  },
  {
    "id": 791,
    "question": "bajar",
    "questionDetails": "La bibliotecaria le pidió a Jonathan que bajara la voz.",
    "answer": "lower, drop, climb down",
    "answerDetails": "The librarian asked Jonathan to lower his voice."
  },
  {
    "id": 792,
    "question": "pequeño",
    "questionDetails": "Cortar el okra hasta pequeño.",
    "answer": "small, little",
    "answerDetails": "Cut the okra up small."
  },
  {
    "id": 793,
    "question": "información",
    "questionDetails": "No pudo recopilar toda la información necesaria para su trabajo.",
    "answer": "information",
    "answerDetails": "She couldn’t gather all the necessary information for her Paper."
  },
  {
    "id": 794,
    "question": "entiendes",
    "questionDetails": "Sé que entiendes lo que digo, ¿no es así?",
    "answer": "you understand, you know it",
    "answerDetails": "I know you understand what I say, don’t you?"
  },
  {
    "id": 795,
    "question": "ocurre",
    "questionDetails": "Una apoplejía puede ser fatal. Ocurre cuando el flujo sanguíneo a una zona del cerebro se interrumpe.",
    "answer": "it occurs",
    "answerDetails": "A stroke can be fatal. It occurs when blood flow to an area of the brain is interrupted."
  },
  {
    "id": 796,
    "question": "ganar",
    "questionDetails": "Los dólares pueden ser colocados en el depósito y ganar interés.",
    "answer": "earn, gain",
    "answerDetails": "The dollars can be placed on deposit and earn interest."
  },
  {
    "id": 797,
    "question": "preguntas",
    "questionDetails": "La policía quiere hacerte unas preguntas.",
    "answer": "some questions",
    "answerDetails": "The police want to ask you some questions."
  },
  {
    "id": 798,
    "question": "dieron",
    "questionDetails": "Dieron sus estanterías a Sarah cuando se mudaron.",
    "answer": "they gave",
    "answerDetails": "They gave Sarah their bookshelves when they moved."
  },
  {
    "id": 799,
    "question": "sigo",
    "questionDetails": "Yo sigo mi instinto, y eso siempre funcionó.",
    "answer": "follow, still",
    "answerDetails": "I follow my instincts, it’s always worked before."
  },
  {
    "id": 800,
    "question": "preguntar",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo quiero preguntar sobre el bosque de mi padre.",
    "answer": "ask",
    "answerDetails": "I just want to ask about my father’s forest."
  },
  {
    "id": 801,
    "question": "habían",
    "questionDetails": "Ellos habían sido mis más queridos amigos.",
    "answer": "had, ‘d",
    "answerDetails": "They had been my dearest friends."
  },
  {
    "id": 802,
    "question": "estés",
    "questionDetails": "Espero que lo estés pasando bien.",
    "answer": "‘re",
    "answerDetails": "Hope you’re having a good time."
  },
  {
    "id": 803,
    "question": "caer",
    "questionDetails": "El costo de la matrícula no debe caer en el estudiante.",
    "answer": "fall, drop",
    "answerDetails": "The cost of tuition should not fall on the student."
  },
  {
    "id": 804,
    "question": "fuerza",
    "questionDetails": "Emplear la fuerza.",
    "answer": "force, strength, power",
    "answerDetails": "To use force."
  },
  {
    "id": 805,
    "question": "deben",
    "questionDetails": "Deben haber tenido una gran cosecha de opio este año.",
    "answer": "must, should",
    "answerDetails": "Must have been a good opium crop this year."
  },
  {
    "id": 806,
    "question": "encuentra",
    "answer": "Find"
  },
  {
    "id": 807,
    "question": "llevas",
    "questionDetails": "Pero siempre lo llevas contigo.",
    "answer": "take, carry",
    "answerDetails": "But you always take it with you."
  },
  {
    "id": 808,
    "question": "corre",
    "questionDetails": "Corre en la playa cada mañana.",
    "answer": "she runs",
    "answerDetails": "She runs on the beach every morning."
  },
  {
    "id": 809,
    "question": "cállate",
    "questionDetails": "Cállate. No quiero que nadie nos oiga.",
    "answer": "keep quiet",
    "answerDetails": "Keep quiet. I don’t want anyone hearing us."
  },
  {
    "id": 810,
    "question": "vienes",
    "answer": "Come"
  },
  {
    "id": 811,
    "question": "abrir",
    "questionDetails": "En cualquier caso, deberíamos abrir las cortinas.",
    "answer": "open",
    "answerDetails": "In any case we should open the curtains."
  },
  {
    "id": 812,
    "question": "cuesta",
    "questionDetails": "Tienes que subir por esa cuesta hasta llegar a la iglesia, y entonces virar a la derecha.",
    "answer": "slope, it costs, incline",
    "answerDetails": "You need to go up that slope until you reach the church, and then to turn right."
  },
  {
    "id": 813,
    "question": "piensas",
    "questionDetails": "Y en serio piensas.",
    "answer": "think",
    "answerDetails": "And you really think."
  },
  {
    "id": 814,
    "question": "error",
    "questionDetails": "Tiene que haber algún error. Yo nunca he estado en Arizona.",
    "answer": "mistake",
    "answerDetails": "There must be some mistake. I’ve never been to Arizona."
  },
  {
    "id": 815,
    "question": "grupo",
    "questionDetails": "Terapia de grupo.",
    "answer": "group, pool, team",
    "answerDetails": "Group therapy."
  },
  {
    "id": 816,
    "question": "iban",
    "answer": "IBAN"
  },
  {
    "id": 817,
    "question": "suena",
    "answer": "Sounds"
  },
  {
    "id": 818,
    "question": "hablado",
    "questionDetails": "Tu padre jamás habría hablado de esta manera.",
    "answer": "spoken",
    "answerDetails": "Your father would never have spoken this way."
  },
  {
    "id": 819,
    "question": "piso",
    "questionDetails": "Vivo en el cuarto piso, al lado del gimnasio.",
    "answer": "floor, apartment",
    "answerDetails": "I live on the fourth floor, next to the gym."
  },
  {
    "id": 820,
    "question": "parar",
    "questionDetails": "Esto tiene que parar y tiene que parar ahora.",
    "answer": "stop",
    "answerDetails": "This has to stop and it has to stop now."
  },
  {
    "id": 821,
    "question": "usar",
    "questionDetails": "Podrías usar mi nombre, si saben que trabajas para mí, podrían abrir.",
    "answer": "use",
    "answerDetails": "You could use my name—if they know you work for me, they might open up."
  },
  {
    "id": 822,
    "question": "nueve",
    "questionDetails": "Las mujeres se vestían a los nueves.",
    "answer": "nine",
    "answerDetails": "The women were dressed to the nines."
  },
  {
    "id": 823,
    "question": "doctor",
    "questionDetails": "Ve a ver a un doctor.",
    "answer": "doctor, Dr, doc",
    "answerDetails": "Go see a doctor."
  },
  {
    "id": 824,
    "question": "hospital",
    "questionDetails": "El hospital donde trabaja está cerca de aquí.",
    "answer": "hospital",
    "answerDetails": "The hospital he works at is right near here."
  },
  {
    "id": 825,
    "question": "temprano",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero terminar el trabajo temprano hoy.",
    "answer": "early",
    "answerDetails": "I want to finish work early today."
  },
  {
    "id": 826,
    "question": "ojo",
    "questionDetails": "Este éxito para Manchester es uno en el ojo para Londres.",
    "answer": "eye, keyhole",
    "answerDetails": "This success for Manchester is one in the eye for London."
  },
  {
    "id": 827,
    "question": "estará",
    "questionDetails": "¿Cuándo estará listo? Tenemos que irnos pronto.",
    "answer": "will you be",
    "answerDetails": "When will you be ready? We need to leave soon."
  },
  {
    "id": 828,
    "question": "novio",
    "questionDetails": "Conoció a su novio en Europa y ya llevan un año juntos.",
    "answer": "boyfriend",
    "answerDetails": "She met her boyfriend in Europe and they’ve been together a year now."
  },
  {
    "id": 829,
    "question": "orden",
    "questionDetails": "El Tribunal emitió una orden para conceder la petición de auto de avocación.",
    "answer": "order, warrant",
    "answerDetails": "The court issued an order granting the petition for a writ of certiorari."
  },
  {
    "id": 830,
    "question": "estaría",
    "questionDetails": "El mundo estaría mejor sin ti.",
    "answer": "be",
    "answerDetails": "The whole world will be better off without you."
  },
  {
    "id": 831,
    "question": "metido",
    "questionDetails": "Cualquiera que se haya metido conmigo en un salón.",
    "answer": "messed, tucked, got",
    "answerDetails": "Everybody who’s ever messed with me in one room."
  },
  {
    "id": 832,
    "question": "pensado",
    "answer": "Thought"
  },
  {
    "id": 833,
    "question": "llegué",
    "questionDetails": "Parece que llegué en un momento interesante.",
    "answer": "arrived, got",
    "answerDetails": "I seem to have arrived at an interesting moment."
  },
  {
    "id": 834,
    "question": "aprender",
    "questionDetails": "Empezaron a aprender francés.",
    "answer": "learn",
    "answerDetails": "They’d started learning French."
  },
  {
    "id": 835,
    "question": "necesitas",
    "answer": "Need"
  },
  {
    "id": 836,
    "question": "quedamos",
    "answer": "Were"
  },
  {
    "id": 837,
    "question": "propia",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero mi propia casa, mis propios amigos.",
    "answer": "own",
    "answerDetails": "I want my own friends."
  },
  {
    "id": 838,
    "question": "corriendo",
    "questionDetails": "Sigue corriendo hasta que no tengas hambre.",
    "answer": "running, rushing, hurrying",
    "answerDetails": "Keep running until you’re not hungry."
  },
  {
    "id": 839,
    "question": "zona",
    "questionDetails": "Hay varias zonas verdes en la ciudad.",
    "answer": "area, district",
    "answerDetails": "There are several green areas in the city."
  },
  {
    "id": 840,
    "question": "sabías",
    "questionDetails": "Si sabías que era una mala idea, ¿por qué lo hicisite?",
    "answer": "you knew, did you know",
    "answerDetails": "If you knew that this was a bad idea, why did you do it?"
  },
  {
    "id": 841,
    "question": "mesa",
    "questionDetails": "A la mesa.",
    "answer": "table",
    "answerDetails": "At table."
  },
  {
    "id": 842,
    "question": "seguramente",
    "questionDetails": "Si no hay voluntad, entonces seguramente la casa va automáticamente a usted.",
    "answer": "surely, probably",
    "answerDetails": "If there is no will, then surely the house goes automatically to you."
  },
  {
    "id": 843,
    "question": "noticia",
    "answer": "item"
  },
  {
    "id": 844,
    "question": "prefiero",
    "answer": "i would rather"
  },
  {
    "id": 845,
    "question": "habría",
    "questionDetails": "De destruir el prototipo, la compañía habría quebrado.",
    "answer": "would",
    "answerDetails": "With the destroyed archetype company would go the bankruptcy."
  },
  {
    "id": 846,
    "question": "llego",
    "questionDetails": "El otro auto llego como hace media hora.",
    "answer": "arrived, came",
    "answerDetails": "The other car arrived half an hour ago."
  },
  {
    "id": 847,
    "question": "llamada",
    "questionDetails": "Los caminantes no pueden resistir la llamada de los Cairngorms.",
    "answer": "call",
    "answerDetails": "Walkers can’t resist the call of the Cairngorms."
  },
  {
    "id": 848,
    "question": "pudo",
    "questionDetails": "Hizo lo mejor que pudo, pero otro ganó.",
    "answer": "he could, he was able, could you",
    "answerDetails": "He did the best he could, but someone else won."
  },
  {
    "id": 849,
    "question": "cuentas",
    "questionDetails": "Mi mamá lleva las cuentas en un despacho de abogados.",
    "answer": "accounts",
    "answerDetails": "My mom keeps the accounts for a law firm."
  },
  {
    "id": 850,
    "question": "cualquiera",
    "questionDetails": "Cualquiera que quiera postularse para el puesto debe tener el doctorado.",
    "answer": "anyone, either, whichever",
    "answerDetails": "Anyone who wants to apply for the position must have a PhD."
  },
  {
    "id": 851,
    "question": "quedé",
    "questionDetails": "Yo me quedé aquí.",
    "answer": "stayed, was, stood",
    "answerDetails": "I just stayed put myself."
  },
  {
    "id": 852,
    "question": "eras",
    "questionDetails": "Tú eras como un hermano para mí.",
    "answer": "were, ages",
    "answerDetails": "You were like a brother to me."
  },
  {
    "id": 853,
    "question": "llevamos",
    "questionDetails": "Llevamos la leña dentro porque iba a llover.",
    "answer": "we carried",
    "answerDetails": "We carried the firewood inside because it was going to rain."
  },
  {
    "id": 854,
    "question": "ey",
    "answer": "Hey"
  },
  {
    "id": 855,
    "question": "equipo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Cuál es tu equipo de fútbol preferido?",
    "answer": "team, system, crew",
    "answerDetails": "What’s your favorite soccer team?"
  },
  {
    "id": 856,
    "question": "pidió",
    "questionDetails": "Tenía hambre, así que pidió una pizza.",
    "answer": "he ordered, he asked for, you asked for",
    "answerDetails": "He was hungry so he ordered a pizza."
  },
  {
    "id": 857,
    "question": "prueba",
    "questionDetails": "Poner algo/a alguien a prueba.",
    "answer": "test, proof, trial",
    "answerDetails": "To put something/somebody to the test."
  },
  {
    "id": 858,
    "question": "funciona",
    "answer": "Works"
  },
  {
    "id": 859,
    "question": "llorar",
    "questionDetails": "Si quieres llorar está bien.",
    "answer": "cry",
    "answerDetails": "If you want to cry, it’s okay."
  },
  {
    "id": 860,
    "question": "quede",
    "questionDetails": "Yo quizá me quede a esperar con él.",
    "answer": "stay, is",
    "answerDetails": "I might stay and wait with him."
  },
  {
    "id": 861,
    "question": "supongo",
    "questionDetails": "Supongo chicos que no sabían del ascensor.",
    "answer": "guess, I’m guessing, suppose",
    "answerDetails": "Guess you guys didn’t know about the elevator."
  },
  {
    "id": 862,
    "question": "escuela",
    "questionDetails": "Louis Sullivan es mi arquitecto favorito de la escuela de Chicago.",
    "answer": "school, training",
    "answerDetails": "Louis Sullivan is my favorite architect of the Chicago School."
  },
  {
    "id": 863,
    "question": "próxima",
    "questionDetails": "Intenta que sea una visita más larga la próxima vez.",
    "answer": "next, upcoming, forthcoming",
    "answerDetails": "Plan on a longer visit next time."
  },
  {
    "id": 864,
    "question": "trabaja",
    "answer": "Works"
  },
  {
    "id": 865,
    "question": "negro",
    "questionDetails": "Una taza de café negro.",
    "answer": "black, dark",
    "answerDetails": "A mug of black coffee."
  },
  {
    "id": 866,
    "question": "ante",
    "questionDetails": "Ante tu problema, el mío es una tontería.",
    "answer": "compared to",
    "answerDetails": "Compared to your problem, mine seems silly."
  },
  {
    "id": 867,
    "question": "llevó",
    "questionDetails": "Llevó la caja abajo y la dejó junto a la puerta.",
    "answer": "he carried, he led, he wore",
    "answerDetails": "He carried the box downstairs and left it by the door."
  },
  {
    "id": 868,
    "question": "control",
    "questionDetails": "Te lo juro, hay que ser ingeniero espacial para programar este control.",
    "answer": "remote, monitoring, check",
    "answerDetails": "I swear, you have to be a rocket scientist to program this remote."
  },
  {
    "id": 869,
    "question": "incluso",
    "questionDetails": "Es incluso peor de lo que parece.",
    "answer": "even, including",
    "answerDetails": "It is even worse than it looks."
  },
  {
    "id": 870,
    "question": "imagino",
    "questionDetails": "Me imagino que las haría.",
    "answer": "imagine, guess, fancy",
    "answerDetails": "I imagine it would."
  },
  {
    "id": 871,
    "question": "coche",
    "questionDetails": "Estaba en el ascensor cuando el coche atascado.",
    "answer": "car, coach",
    "answerDetails": "He was in the lift when the car stuck."
  },
  {
    "id": 872,
    "question": "viva",
    "questionDetails": "Esa gente está viva.",
    "answer": "alive, live, vivid",
    "answerDetails": "Those people are alive."
  },
  {
    "id": 873,
    "question": "apenas",
    "questionDetails": "Asintió con la cabeza, apenas capaz de hablar.",
    "answer": "barely, scarcely",
    "answerDetails": "She nodded, barely able to speak."
  },
  {
    "id": 874,
    "question": "deberías",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo creo que deberías tener cuidado.",
    "answer": "should",
    "answerDetails": "I just think you should be careful."
  },
  {
    "id": 875,
    "question": "echar",
    "questionDetails": "Vas a echar por tierra todo lo que planeamos.",
    "answer": "throw",
    "answerDetails": "You going to throw out everything we planned."
  },
  {
    "id": 876,
    "question": "suyo",
    "questionDetails": "Usted suelte el suyo.",
    "answer": "yours",
    "answerDetails": "You let yours go!"
  },
  {
    "id": 877,
    "question": "llamó",
    "answer": "i call her"
  },
  {
    "id": 878,
    "question": "sean",
    "questionDetails": "Partiendo del supuesto de que los aros sean una firma.",
    "answer": "are",
    "answerDetails": "Working from the assumption the rings are a signature."
  },
  {
    "id": 879,
    "question": "habíamos",
    "questionDetails": "Hice lo que habíamos planeado.",
    "answer": "had",
    "answerDetails": "I did what we had planned."
  },
  {
    "id": 880,
    "question": "prometo",
    "questionDetails": "Prometo no volver a mentir.",
    "answer": "i promise",
    "answerDetails": "I promise that I’ll never lie again."
  },
  {
    "id": 881,
    "question": "contrario",
    "questionDetails": "Continuó bebiendo a pesar de Consejo médico al contrario.",
    "answer": "contrary",
    "answerDetails": "He continued to drink despite medical advice to the contrary."
  },
  {
    "id": 882,
    "question": "sitio",
    "questionDetails": "El hormigón se mezcla en el sitio.",
    "answer": "site",
    "answerDetails": "The concrete is mixed on site."
  },
  {
    "id": 883,
    "question": "gustó",
    "questionDetails": "Realmente me gustó tu obra.",
    "answer": "liked, enjoyed, appreciated",
    "answerDetails": "I really liked your play."
  },
  {
    "id": 884,
    "question": "quiénes",
    "questionDetails": "Les dije quiénes somos.",
    "answer": "who",
    "answerDetails": "I told them who we are."
  },
  {
    "id": 885,
    "question": "duda",
    "questionDetails": "Sin duda.",
    "answer": "doubt, question",
    "answerDetails": "No doubt."
  },
  {
    "id": 886,
    "question": "cielo",
    "questionDetails": "Cientos de estrellas brillaban en el cielo.",
    "answer": "sky, heaven, god",
    "answerDetails": "Hundreds of stars were shining in the sky."
  },
  {
    "id": 887,
    "question": "tendría",
    "questionDetails": "Le dije a Fernanda que comprara acciones de la empresa. Ahora tendría mucho dinero si lo hubiera hecho.",
    "answer": "she would have, we would have",
    "answerDetails": "I told Fernanda to buy shares of the company. She would have a lot of money now if she had."
  },
  {
    "id": 888,
    "question": "cayó",
    "questionDetails": "Cayó de un andamio y fue trasladado al hospital.",
    "answer": "he fell down",
    "answerDetails": "He fell down from a scaffold and was taken to the hospital."
  },
  {
    "id": 889,
    "question": "varios",
    "questionDetails": "Varios de sus amigos asistieron.",
    "answer": "several",
    "answerDetails": "Several of his friends attended."
  },
  {
    "id": 890,
    "question": "puse",
    "questionDetails": "Yo la puse ahí.",
    "answer": "put, wore, laid",
    "answerDetails": "I put it there."
  },
  {
    "id": 891,
    "question": "pedido",
    "questionDetails": "La entrega de su pedido está retrasado.",
    "answer": "order",
    "answerDetails": "The delivery of your order is delayed."
  },
  {
    "id": 892,
    "question": "partes",
    "questionDetails": "Son dos partes separadas de su ser.",
    "answer": "parts, parties, sides",
    "answerDetails": "They are two separate parts of his being."
  },
  {
    "id": 893,
    "question": "esposa",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero bailar con mi esposa.",
    "answer": "wife, spouse, bride",
    "answerDetails": "I want to dance with my wife."
  },
  {
    "id": 894,
    "question": "tía",
    "questionDetails": "Entonces mi tía insistió en tener un ataúd abierto.",
    "answer": "aunt, auntie, aunty",
    "answerDetails": "Then my aunt insisted on having an open casket."
  },
  {
    "id": 895,
    "question": "decisión",
    "questionDetails": "He tomado una decisión; trabajaré con mi padre.",
    "answer": "decision, ruling",
    "answerDetails": "I have made my decision; I’m going to work with my father."
  },
  {
    "id": 896,
    "question": "ellas",
    "questionDetails": "Ellas son hermanas.",
    "answer": "they",
    "answerDetails": "They are sisters."
  },
  {
    "id": 897,
    "question": "traer",
    "questionDetails": "Ella no podía traer a sí misma para mencionarlo.",
    "answer": "bring, fetch",
    "answerDetails": "She could not bring herself to mention it."
  },
  {
    "id": 898,
    "question": "sol",
    "questionDetails": "Al sol.",
    "answer": "sun",
    "answerDetails": "In the sun."
  },
  {
    "id": 899,
    "question": "sientes",
    "questionDetails": "Dile cómo te sientes.",
    "answer": "feel",
    "answerDetails": "Tell her how you feel."
  },
  {
    "id": 900,
    "question": "saliendo",
    "questionDetails": "Con razón no estás saliendo con nadie.",
    "answer": "dating, leaving, departing",
    "answerDetails": "No wonder you’re not dating anyone."
  },
  {
    "id": 901,
    "question": "cae",
    "questionDetails": "Cada vez que cae una dinastía.",
    "answer": "falls, drops, tumbles",
    "answerDetails": "Each time a dynasty falls."
  },
  {
    "id": 902,
    "question": "tenían",
    "questionDetails": "Después del silbato del comienzo se tenían que ir todos.",
    "answer": "had",
    "answerDetails": "After the initial whistle all had to leave."
  },
  {
    "id": 903,
    "question": "llamaba",
    "answer": "Called"
  },
  {
    "id": 904,
    "question": "alma",
    "questionDetails": "Llorar es bueno para el alma.",
    "answer": "soul, heart, spirit",
    "answerDetails": "Crying is good for the soul."
  },
  {
    "id": 905,
    "question": "escúchame",
    "questionDetails": "Sólo escúchame y responde.",
    "answer": "listen",
    "answerDetails": "Just listen and answer."
  },
  {
    "id": 906,
    "question": "lindo",
    "questionDetails": "Los dos hermanos eran lo suficientemente lindos para encontrar un par de mujeres ricas y casarse con ellos.",
    "answer": "cute",
    "answerDetails": "The two brothers were cute enough to find a couple of rich women and marry them."
  },
  {
    "id": 907,
    "question": "interesa",
    "questionDetails": "Pero a ambos les interesa.",
    "answer": "interested, interest, care",
    "answerDetails": "But you two are interested."
  },
  {
    "id": 908,
    "question": "vuelva",
    "questionDetails": "Vuelva aquí en una hora, por favor.",
    "answer": "be back, he comes back",
    "answerDetails": "Be back here in an hour, please."
  },
  {
    "id": 909,
    "question": "irme",
    "questionDetails": "Si me obligan a irme.",
    "answer": "go, leave",
    "answerDetails": "And if you make me go."
  },
  {
    "id": 910,
    "question": "solos",
    "questionDetails": "¿Quieren seguirme?-No, gracias. Sabemos llegar solos.",
    "answer": "on our own, by themselves, by ourselves",
    "answerDetails": "Do you want to follow me?-No, thanks. We know how to get there on our own."
  },
  {
    "id": 911,
    "question": "ninguno",
    "questionDetails": "Usted no conoce a ninguno de mis amigos.",
    "answer": "any",
    "answerDetails": "You don’t know any of my friends."
  },
  {
    "id": 912,
    "question": "daba",
    "answer": "i would give"
  },
  {
    "id": 913,
    "question": "negocio",
    "questionDetails": "¿Cómo va el negocio?",
    "answer": "business, deal",
    "answerDetails": "How’s business?"
  },
  {
    "id": 914,
    "question": "linda",
    "answer": "Linda, cutest, prettier"
  },
  {
    "id": 915,
    "question": "grave",
    "questionDetails": "Fue un choque espeluznante, pero su estado no es grave.",
    "answer": "serious, severe, acute",
    "answerDetails": "It was a bad crash, but his condition is not serious."
  },
  {
    "id": 916,
    "question": "hacerle",
    "questionDetails": "Su mano saldrá y podrá hacerle una pregunta.",
    "answer": "ask, make",
    "answerDetails": "Their hand comes out and you can ask it questions."
  },
  {
    "id": 917,
    "question": "traigo",
    "questionDetails": "Esta semana me traigo el cachorro nuevo a casa.",
    "answer": "i am bringing",
    "answerDetails": "I am bringing my new puppy home this week."
  },
  {
    "id": 918,
    "question": "mando",
    "questionDetails": "Hay un mando en la parte superior izquierda del horno con el que puedes programar el reloj automático.",
    "answer": "knob, officer",
    "answerDetails": "There is a knob at the top left of the oven which allows you to set the timer."
  },
  {
    "id": 919,
    "question": "tantas",
    "answer": "as many"
  },
  {
    "id": 920,
    "question": "secreto",
    "questionDetails": "Revelar or contar un secreto a alguien.",
    "answer": "secret, secrecy",
    "answerDetails": "To let somebody into a secret."
  },
  {
    "id": 921,
    "question": "minuto",
    "questionDetails": "Deja reposar el huevo en agua hervida por 10 minutos.",
    "answer": "minute",
    "answerDetails": "Let the egg sit in boiled water for 10 Minutes."
  },
  {
    "id": 922,
    "question": "vista",
    "questionDetails": "Es aconsejable no dejar bolsos a la vista.",
    "answer": "view, sight, eye",
    "answerDetails": "It is advisable not to leave handbags on view."
  },
  {
    "id": 923,
    "question": "fuego",
    "questionDetails": "La policía devolvió el fuego y lo hirió.",
    "answer": "fire, heat, flame",
    "answerDetails": "Police returned fire and wounded him."
  },
  {
    "id": 924,
    "question": "dejan",
    "questionDetails": "Los que nos dejan.",
    "answer": "leave, let, cease",
    "answerDetails": "Those that leave us."
  },
  {
    "id": 925,
    "question": "éramos",
    "questionDetails": "Dijiste que éramos investigadores.",
    "answer": "were",
    "answerDetails": "You said we were investigators."
  },
  {
    "id": 926,
    "question": "cárcel",
    "questionDetails": "Puedes acabar en la cárcel por robo.",
    "answer": "jail, prison",
    "answerDetails": "You can end up in jail for robbery."
  },
  {
    "id": 927,
    "question": "preocupe",
    "questionDetails": "O quizá eso no te preocupe.",
    "answer": "worry",
    "answerDetails": "Or maybe that doesn’t worry you."
  },
  {
    "id": 928,
    "question": "decirte",
    "questionDetails": "Muero por decirte lo que pasó en mi cita Anoche.",
    "answer": "tell you",
    "answerDetails": "I’m dying to tell you what happened on my date last night."
  },
  {
    "id": 929,
    "question": "habitación",
    "questionDetails": "Comparto la habitación con mi hermana pequeña.",
    "answer": "bedroom",
    "answerDetails": "I share my bedroom with my little sister."
  },
  {
    "id": 930,
    "question": "explicar",
    "questionDetails": "Explicarse.",
    "answer": "explain",
    "answerDetails": "To explain oneself."
  },
  {
    "id": 931,
    "question": "nota",
    "questionDetails": "Es un vino sutil con notas de vainilla y limón.",
    "answer": "note, memo, statement",
    "answerDetails": "It’s a subtle wine with notes of Vanilla and lemon."
  },
  {
    "id": 932,
    "question": "quise",
    "questionDetails": "Alguna vez lo quise, pero ya no.",
    "answer": "i loved",
    "answerDetails": "There was a time when I loved him, but I don’t anymore."
  },
  {
    "id": 933,
    "question": "accidente",
    "questionDetails": "Es un milagro que nadie saliera herido del accidente de avión.",
    "answer": "crash, wreck",
    "answerDetails": "It’s a miracle that no one was injured in the plane crash."
  },
  {
    "id": 934,
    "question": "quédate",
    "questionDetails": "Quédate justo sobre mis manos.",
    "answer": "stay, stick",
    "answerDetails": "Stay right on my hands."
  },
  {
    "id": 935,
    "question": "dirección",
    "questionDetails": "“Venerable” era la forma habitual de la dirección de un sacerdote en ese momento.",
    "answer": "address, direction, directorate",
    "answerDetails": "‘Venerable’ was the usual form of address for a priest at that time."
  },
  {
    "id": 936,
    "question": "momentos",
    "answer": "Moments"
  },
  {
    "id": 937,
    "question": "correr",
    "questionDetails": "Debo correr, llego tarde.",
    "answer": "dash",
    "answerDetails": "I must dash, I’m late."
  },
  {
    "id": 938,
    "question": "compañeros",
    "questionDetails": "Los gatos son excelentes compañeros.",
    "answer": "companions, fellows, classmates",
    "answerDetails": "Cats make wonderful companions."
  },
  {
    "id": 939,
    "question": "subir",
    "questionDetails": "Este archivo está tardando mucho en subir.",
    "answer": "upload, climb",
    "answerDetails": "This file is taking ages to upload."
  },
  {
    "id": 940,
    "question": "llena",
    "questionDetails": "Anhelo que su estadía este llena de iluminación.",
    "answer": "filled, full, crowded",
    "answerDetails": "I hope your stay is filled with much enlightenment."
  },
  {
    "id": 941,
    "question": "total",
    "questionDetails": "Intentar convencerla fue una pérdida de tiempo total.",
    "answer": "complete, overall",
    "answerDetails": "Trying to convince her was a complete waste of time."
  },
  {
    "id": 942,
    "question": "idiota",
    "questionDetails": "Arañé el carro de alguien y no le dejé una nota.-Eres idiota.",
    "answer": "schmuck",
    "answerDetails": "I scratched someone’s car and didn’t leave a note.-You schmuck."
  },
  {
    "id": 943,
    "question": "jugando",
    "questionDetails": "Todos jugando al mismo juego.",
    "answer": "playing, toying, playin’",
    "answerDetails": "All playing the same game."
  },
  {
    "id": 944,
    "question": "vergüenza",
    "questionDetails": "La gente hoy no lo considera una vergüenza.",
    "answer": "shame, embarrassment, disgrace",
    "answerDetails": "People today don’t consider it a shame."
  },
  {
    "id": 945,
    "question": "propio",
    "questionDetails": "Por derecho propio.",
    "answer": "own, proper",
    "answerDetails": "In one’s own right."
  },
  {
    "id": 946,
    "question": "salido",
    "questionDetails": "Nunca hemos salido realmente.",
    "answer": "out",
    "answerDetails": "We were never really going out."
  },
  {
    "id": 947,
    "question": "golpe",
    "questionDetails": "José le dio un golpe a Tom en la nariz.",
    "answer": "strike, stroke, swipe",
    "answerDetails": "Jose landed a strike on Tom’s nose."
  },
  {
    "id": 948,
    "question": "pasan",
    "questionDetails": "Los días pasan siempre iguales.",
    "answer": "pass, spend, happen",
    "answerDetails": "The days pass, always the same."
  },
  {
    "id": 949,
    "question": "mirando",
    "questionDetails": "Yo le vi mirando.",
    "answer": "looking, watching, staring",
    "answerDetails": "I saw you looking."
  },
  {
    "id": 950,
    "question": "oiga",
    "answer": "Hey, hear, listen"
  },
  {
    "id": 951,
    "question": "sepa",
    "questionDetails": "Busquen a gente que sepa.",
    "answer": "know",
    "answerDetails": "Seek out people who know."
  },
  {
    "id": 952,
    "question": "hable",
    "answer": "Talk"
  },
  {
    "id": 953,
    "question": "placer",
    "questionDetails": "Le preguntó si podría tener el placer de llevarla a almorzar.",
    "answer": "pleasure, treat, joy",
    "answerDetails": "He asked if he might have the pleasure of taking her to lunch."
  },
  {
    "id": 954,
    "question": "hagan",
    "questionDetails": "Hagan lo que puedan.",
    "answer": "do, make",
    "answerDetails": "Do the best you can."
  },
  {
    "id": 955,
    "question": "habías",
    "questionDetails": "Pensé que lo habías hecho.",
    "answer": "you",
    "answerDetails": "I thought you did it."
  },
  {
    "id": 956,
    "question": "pareja",
    "questionDetails": "Mi pareja y yo estamos pensando en comprar una casa juntos.",
    "answer": "partner, mate",
    "answerDetails": "My partner and I are considering buying a house together."
  },
  {
    "id": 957,
    "question": "volvió",
    "questionDetails": "Volvió de su viaje de servicio con una perspectiva del mundo muy diferente.",
    "answer": "she returned",
    "answerDetails": "She returned from her service trip with a very different perspective on the world."
  },
  {
    "id": 958,
    "question": "conocí",
    "questionDetails": "Nunca lo conocí en la vida real.",
    "answer": "met, knew",
    "answerDetails": "I never met the man in my life."
  },
  {
    "id": 959,
    "question": "broma",
    "questionDetails": "Los otros estaban jugando una broma en su.",
    "answer": "joke, prank, gag",
    "answerDetails": "The others were playing a joke on her."
  },
  {
    "id": 960,
    "question": "derecha",
    "questionDetails": "Hicieron una serie ordenada de pases por encima de la derecha.",
    "answer": "right, forehand",
    "answerDetails": "They made a neat series of passes over on the right."
  },
  {
    "id": 961,
    "question": "perdóname",
    "questionDetails": "Perdóname. No era mi intención hacerte daño.",
    "answer": "forgive me, pardon me",
    "answerDetails": "Forgive me. I didn’t mean to hurt you."
  },
  {
    "id": 962,
    "question": "rico",
    "questionDetails": "La carga de impuestos sobre los ricos.",
    "answer": "wealthy, delicious",
    "answerDetails": "The burden of taxation on the wealthy."
  },
  {
    "id": 963,
    "question": "terminó",
    "questionDetails": "El encantamiento empezó y terminó en el jardín.",
    "answer": "ended, ended up, finished",
    "answerDetails": "The enchantment began and ended in the grove."
  },
  {
    "id": 964,
    "question": "cocina",
    "questionDetails": "Pasamos la noche probando la cocina local.",
    "answer": "cuisine, stove",
    "answerDetails": "We spent the evening sampling the local cuisine."
  },
  {
    "id": 965,
    "question": "varias",
    "questionDetails": "Existen varias razones para que esto suceda.",
    "answer": "several",
    "answerDetails": "There are several reasons for this."
  },
  {
    "id": 966,
    "question": "gustaba",
    "questionDetails": "Me gustaba la composición.",
    "answer": "liked, enjoyed",
    "answerDetails": "I liked the arrangement."
  },
  {
    "id": 967,
    "question": "hotel",
    "questionDetails": "Ese era el camarero del hotel.",
    "answer": "hotel",
    "answerDetails": "That was the waiter from the hotel."
  },
  {
    "id": 968,
    "question": "resulta",
    "questionDetails": "Pero ya ves, cada cosa resulta de lo mejor.",
    "answer": "turns out, resulting, is",
    "answerDetails": "But you see, every thing turns out for the best."
  },
  {
    "id": 969,
    "question": "hermanos",
    "questionDetails": "Mis hermanos siempre me toman el pelo.",
    "answer": "brothers, siblings",
    "answerDetails": "My brothers are always teasing me."
  },
  {
    "id": 970,
    "question": "perdona",
    "questionDetails": "Algunos dicen olvida y perdona.",
    "answer": "forgive, sorry, excuse me",
    "answerDetails": "Some people say forgive and forget."
  },
  {
    "id": 971,
    "question": "yendo",
    "questionDetails": "El contrato que mencionó antes está yendo bien.",
    "answer": "going, leaving, heading",
    "answerDetails": "The contract that you mentioned earlier is going well."
  },
  {
    "id": 972,
    "question": "totalmente",
    "questionDetails": "Estaba totalmente agotado cuando regresamos a casa del Aeropuerto.",
    "answer": "fully, totally, completely",
    "answerDetails": "I was fully exhausted when we got home from the airport."
  },
  {
    "id": 973,
    "question": "conocido",
    "questionDetails": "Estarás trabajando con Fernando en este proyecto. ¿Lo conoces?-Sí, somos conocidos.",
    "answer": "acquainted",
    "answerDetails": "You’ll be working with Fernando on this project. Do you know him?-Yes, we’re acquainted."
  },
  {
    "id": 974,
    "question": "parecía",
    "questionDetails": "Parecía más flaca con ese vestido.",
    "answer": "she looked, he appeared, it looked like",
    "answerDetails": "She looked skinnier in that dress."
  },
  {
    "id": 975,
    "question": "quisiera",
    "questionDetails": "Quisiera ganar la lotería para no tener que trabajar más.",
    "answer": "i would like",
    "answerDetails": "I would like to win the lottery so that I don’t have to work anymore."
  },
  {
    "id": 976,
    "question": "trato",
    "questionDetails": "Hacer un trato.",
    "answer": "deal, bargain",
    "answerDetails": "To do a deal."
  },
  {
    "id": 977,
    "question": "disculpe",
    "questionDetails": "Disculpe, ¿es este el tren para ir a Nueva York?",
    "answer": "excuse me, pardon me, forgive me",
    "answerDetails": "Excuse me. Is this the right train for New York?"
  },
  {
    "id": 978,
    "question": "pidiendo",
    "questionDetails": "Nadie le está pidiendo que lo haga.",
    "answer": "asking, requesting, begging",
    "answerDetails": "And no one is asking you to."
  },
  {
    "id": 979,
    "question": "pies",
    "questionDetails": "Ah, tengo los pies hinchados.",
    "answer": "feet",
    "answerDetails": "My feet are swelling."
  },
  {
    "id": 980,
    "question": "asunto",
    "questionDetails": "Los británicos se les da la preeminencia en el asunto del té.",
    "answer": "matter, subject, issue",
    "answerDetails": "The British are given pre-eminence in the matter of tea."
  },
  {
    "id": 981,
    "question": "cargo",
    "questionDetails": "La acusación presentó los cargos al jurado.",
    "answer": "charge, office, position",
    "answerDetails": "The prosecution presented the charges to the jury."
  },
  {
    "id": 982,
    "question": "precisamente",
    "questionDetails": "Tienes que decirnos precisamente lo que quieres que hagamos, para que no nos equivoquemos.",
    "answer": "precisely",
    "answerDetails": "You have to tell us precisely what you want us to do, so we don’t make mistakes."
  },
  {
    "id": 983,
    "question": "arreglar",
    "questionDetails": "Te arreglaré con una habitación.",
    "answer": "fix, mend",
    "answerDetails": "I’ll fix you up with a room."
  },
  {
    "id": 984,
    "question": "reunión",
    "questionDetails": "Se convocó una reunión del personal docente para discutir el presupuesto.",
    "answer": "conference, reunion",
    "answerDetails": "A Staff Conference was convened to discuss the budget."
  },
  {
    "id": 985,
    "question": "pedí",
    "questionDetails": "Le pedí ver sus informes psiquiátricos.",
    "answer": "asked, ordered",
    "answerDetails": "I asked to see his psychiatric reports."
  },
  {
    "id": 986,
    "question": "manda",
    "questionDetails": "Ana dejó una manda de 100 hectáreas a sus nietos.",
    "answer": "bequest",
    "answerDetails": "Ana left a bequest of 100 hectares to her grandchildren."
  },
  {
    "id": 987,
    "question": "haría",
    "questionDetails": "Me imagino que las haría.",
    "answer": "would",
    "answerDetails": "I imagine it would."
  },
  {
    "id": 988,
    "question": "tiro",
    "questionDetails": "Cada uno de sus tiros alcanzó al plato.",
    "answer": "shot, throw, kick",
    "answerDetails": "Every one of his shots hit a clay pigeon."
  },
  {
    "id": 989,
    "question": "viviendo",
    "questionDetails": "Mi padre cree que viviendo experiencias difíciles una persona se vuelve más fuerte.",
    "answer": "by having",
    "answerDetails": "My father believes that by having difficult experiences, a person becomes stronger."
  },
  {
    "id": 990,
    "question": "público",
    "questionDetails": "Todo oficial público recibirá un aguinaldo de 5000 pesos.",
    "answer": "public",
    "answerDetails": "All public servants will receive a Christmas bonus of 5000 pesos."
  },
  {
    "id": 991,
    "question": "pago",
    "questionDetails": "Impago M.",
    "answer": "payment, payout",
    "answerDetails": "Non payment."
  },
  {
    "id": 992,
    "question": "locura",
    "questionDetails": "La locura de mi padre evolucionaba a medida que envejecía.",
    "answer": "madness, insanity, folly",
    "answerDetails": "My father’s madness progressed as he got older."
  },
  {
    "id": 993,
    "question": "tomando",
    "answer": "by having"
  },
  {
    "id": 994,
    "question": "real",
    "questionDetails": "La estimación era mucho menor que el costo real.",
    "answer": "actual, royal, true",
    "answerDetails": "The estimate was much less than the actual cost."
  },
  {
    "id": 995,
    "question": "pequeña",
    "questionDetails": "De pequeña, me encantaba escuchar sus cuentos.",
    "answer": "little girl, petite",
    "answerDetails": "When I was a little girl I loved to hear her stories."
  },
  {
    "id": 996,
    "question": "oficina",
    "questionDetails": "Fue expulsado de la oficina en 1988.",
    "answer": "office, bureau",
    "answerDetails": "He was ejected from office in 1988."
  },
  {
    "id": 997,
    "question": "siga",
    "answer": "drive on"
  },
  {
    "id": 998,
    "question": "guerra",
    "questionDetails": "La guerra ha costado las vidas de miles de soldados y civiles.",
    "answer": "war",
    "answerDetails": "The war has cost thousands of soldiers and civilians their lives."
  },
  {
    "id": 999,
    "question": "imbécil",
    "questionDetails": "Oye, algún imbécil está meando en el pasillo de tu edificio.",
    "answer": "dickhead, prick",
    "answerDetails": "Hey, some dickhead is peeing in the hallway of your building."
  },
  {
    "id": 1000,
    "question": "aparte",
    "questionDetails": "Bromas aparte, hacen un trabajo realmente notable.",
    "answer": "apart, aside, separate",
    "answerDetails": "Joking apart, they do a really remarkable job."
  }
]
